PAT: What, are you kidding me? Sundays? I love Sundays. I live for Sundays.
开什么玩笑  星期天？ 我爱星期天
每天都盼着星期天
The whole family's together. Mom makes braciole. Dad puts the jersey on.
全家人聚在一起  妈妈做了酒烩肉卷
爸爸穿上球衣
We're all watching the game. Yeah, it drives me crazy, and yes,
我们都在看球赛  对  这快把我逼疯了
I was negative. You didn't even know that I loved it, Nikki, but I did.
我很消极  但你不知道我喜欢这些  尼基
I just didn't appreciate it, or you, before. ?
只是过去没有好好珍惜  也没有珍惜你
Come on. Time to go.
快点  该走了
I lost all that. I blew it. But you also blew it. We can get it back.
我失去了一切  罪有应得  可你也有错
We're gonna get it back. It's all gonna be better now.
我们能重新开始
I'm better now and I hope you are, too. And I'm gonna appreciate--?
我们会重新开始  一切都会好起来
我好多了  希望你也是  我会好好珍惜
Hey, I'll be there in a minute, okay?
马上就好  好吗
Doctor's waiting. Let's go.
医生等着呢  快走
I'll be there in a minute.
一会儿就到
That's true love.
Subtitles downloaded from Podnapisi.NET
这是真爱
「精进不休」
DANNY: Yeah, that's when I had long hair. People say I talk about my hair too much.
And it was just the way I wanted it, but he cut it back too far.
那时我头发很长  他们说我总讨论发型
He cut this side back too far trying to even it up. I didn't tell him to do that.
可我就喜欢那一款  他把这边剪得很短
I said, Just cut it the way you cut it... . ?
只好把另一边多剪点
PAT: Once you get in the right frame of mind, I think anything's possible.
我可没叫他这样剪
I think we get, we so often get caught in this state of negativity and
我说的是  就按你上次剪的那样
只要思路对了  一切皆有可能
it's a, it's a poison like nothing else.
我觉得  我们总会陷入消极状态
这是一种毒药  好像什么都无所谓
DR. TIMBERS:... technically, you can take him out against our recommendation,
but you assume a lot of liability in the eyes of the court.
程序上  您可以不顾我们的忠告把他带走
And he's just getting used to the routine here.
DOLORES: I don't want him to get used to the routine here.
但您将在法律上承担主要责任
况且他刚刚习惯这里的生活
Eight months is already long enough.
我才不希望他习惯这里的生活
八个月已经够长了
「出院许可」
「院方不承担任何责任」
PAT: Hey, Mom. Can we give Danny a ride to North Philly?
DOLORES: What? I don't understand.
妈  把丹尼载到费城北区可以吗？
PAT: Mom, no, it'll be fine. It'll be fine.
DANNY: I guess everybody's leaving today!
什么  为什么？
Hello, Mrs. S. An honor to finally meet you. Pat told me all about you,
妈  没关系  没关系的
我猜大家今天都能出院啊
how God made you rich in character, and you're the mighty oak that holds
夫人  您好  终于有幸见到您了
the household together, and not to mention the lasagna you make on game day
帕特常跟我提起您
when the Birds play.
他说您超有个性  简直是家里的顶梁柱
做的卤汁面更是一绝
PAT: Danny was in for assault because of crystal meth and alcohol.
DANNY: Bad combination.
Yeah. On top of an anxiety disorder. That was when I was an X-ray
technician with my ADD and my anxiety. I had a lot of access to
丹尼吸毒酗酒时才会打架
才不是这么回事
medication and I took advantage of it. That's when my hair was long, too.
- 主要还是焦虑症 - 我以前是个放射技师
又有焦虑症  有很多机会弄到药
But my hair only grew when I was older. When I was younger, my
hair didn't grow because my brother...
那时我头发很长
Remember I told you about my brother, he had a Jheri curl, and
I couldn't get a Jheri curl because my hair didn't grow long enough.
我年纪大了才开始留头发
I was so jealous of my brother...
小时候没留过  因为我哥…
But Wait a minute, Wait a minute. Hello?
我跟你说过  我哥烫过杰里卷
Yeah! It looks great now. You like it?
我头发不够长  烫不了
No, It's good now. Yes, it is.
Wait, you're going the wrong way!
就很嫉妒他
What? Are you sure about that? I'll bring him back right away.
- 先等我讲完 - 喂？
- 这样挺好的 - 真的？
You lied to me, Pat. Danny's not allowed to leave.
- 现在这样就不错 - 是挺不错
等等  你摸错方向了
什么  你确定？ 我这就把他送回去
All right, Mom, just hold on a sec.
Let's just talk about this.
Mom, just listen-- Don't tou-...
你骗我  帕特  丹尼明明不能出院
... -ch the steering... ... wheel!
Pat, this whole thing was a mistake.
妈  等一下
我们谈谈
I'm sorry, Mom. You okay?
- 妈  听我说 - 别动方向盘  放手！
I am out on a limb for you with the courts right now.
帕特  整件事就是个误会
It's my fault. Pat didn't know. Pat didn't know. He's my friend,
so he was rootin' for me. I'm havin' a disagreement with the hospital,
妈妈  对不起  你没事吧？
but we're working it out. Take me back to the hospital,
我担心法庭会找你麻烦
but take Pat home, he's fine. Trust me. You'll see,
都是我的错  和帕特无关  他什么都不知道
he's fine. It's my fault.
他只是想帮我  我跟医院有点小矛盾
Mom, can we stop at the library? I wanna read Nikki's entire English high school syllabus.
但我会解决的  送我回医院吧
把帕特带回家  相信我  他真的没事
Mom, it's a good thing. I'm remaking myself.
都是我的错
妈  去一下图书馆行吗？
我想看完尼基高中英文教学大纲上的书
妈  这是好事  我要重新开始
DeSean Jackson. What happened to DeSean Jackson?
Come on, tell me that one.
It's insanity. He spikes the ball at the one yard line. The one fucking-yard line.
I mean, get into the end zone, dummy.# I mean, he celebrates before he's even in!
德肖恩・杰克逊
德肖恩・杰克逊怎么了？
You know something? It's nothing new. Your team does that all the time.
快给我讲讲
简直疯了  他在一码线掷地球
They get close...... and then they blow it. They got an inferiority complex.
该死的一码线
Wait a minute, what are you talking about? What makes the Cowboys America's Team?
然后他就进了球门区  蠢货
Because we are, we're America's Team.
没什么好奇怪的  你们队总这样
You should be ashamed of yourself. We're in Philadelphia,
what's the matter with you? You're a fucking traitor.
每次只要一追平  立刻就能搞砸  扶不起来
What's more American than a cowboy?
You know what's more American? What?
瞎说  你们牛仔队凭什么自称美国之队？
Benjamin Franklin, that's what's more American.
Benjamin Franklin?
我们本来就是美国之队
Benjamin Franklin. The founder of our country, here in Philadelphia.
You mean the guy with the... ... little glasses and the long scraggly hair?
你害不害臊  我们可是费城人
What about the lightning with the kite? He stood in the storm with a kite.
搞什么呢  你个叛徒
还有什么比牛仔更能代表美国？
If he wasn't on the hundred dollar bill, nobody... ... would even know who he is.
- 你知道什么叫真正的美国人吗？- 什么？
本杰明・富兰克林  那才是真正的美国人
What are you doing? No, no, no, no. Don't touch them, don't touch them.
本杰明・富兰克林？
I didn't even touch em. Why are you--, don't blame me.
对  他就是在这  在费城缔造了我们国家
Who did this? Who took, who took, who took the...
你是说那个戴着小眼镜  头发乱糟糟的家伙？
the remotes like this? Did you do this, Randy?
那风筝实验呢  他是冒着暴风雨做的实验
No, I dont touch them. As a matter of fact, I dont know why you need so many.
他要不是家财万贯
压根就没人知道他
Hey, there she is! Look how beautiful!
你在干什么  别碰它们
我没碰  少怪到我头上
What!! Whats this?
那是谁干的  谁拿了…
像这样的遥控器  是你吗  兰迪？
没有  我都不知道你怎么那么多遥控器
Everything good? Mm-hmm.
看  美女回来了！
Ahh.
什么  怎么回事？
Where is it? It's right here.
You got it. Ahh, well, we got that. We don't want them to steal that.
You still got yours? Yeah, I got mine.
你还好吗？
So what, you don't talk to me? You didn't tell me you took him out.
Well, he's ready. Look at him.
You didn't tell Dad you were picking me up?
- 那个还在吧？- 在这呢
Don't worry about that. I wanna make sure when you come out
还在  很好  我们还怕让人偷了呢
that you're okay, and she didn't say anything.
You didn't tell me? The court said yes. Don't worry.
- 你的呢？- 我的也在
Yeah, but what did the doctor say? Because the, the court listens to the doctor.
你怎么不跟我商量  你没说要接他出来
Yeah, and the court said- The court listens to the doctor, the doctor-
他已经好了  你看他的样子
Dad, relax. The court said it's fine, okay? Let it go.
你没告诉爸要接我出来？
- 别管这些了 - 我只是想确定…
Don't worry.
你已经完全好了  她什么都没跟我说
Dad, I'm in there because of the court. That's the agreement that we made months ago.
- 你干嘛不告诉我？- 法庭同意了  别担心
It was a plea bargain with the courts.
医生怎么说  法庭得听医生的意见
The lawyer, he instructed me, he said that what we should plead that, and
then I would serve eight months and then I'd get out.
- 没错  法庭说 - 法庭得听医生的
It's all under control.
爸  放松  法庭说没事  好吗？
Well... okay, okay. Congratulations.
别担心
Thank you. So what are you doing with yourself?
爸  是法庭准许我回家的
You know, I'm gonna start a restaurant. It's gonna be a cheesesteak place.
我们几个月前就达成一致了
这是跟法庭的辩诉交易
How you gonna pay for it?
是律师说的  他让我们辩诉
I'm gonna pay for it, don't worry about it.
这样我服刑八个月就能出来了
From your bookmaking?
都是按计划来的
Who told you that? Mom told me. Outside.
I did not. No, I didn't.
好吧  恭喜你
You just told me outside, Mom, what are you talking about?
Five minutes ago, we were walking up the stairs, you said, Don't say anything,
but Dad lost his job and he's bookmaking. ?
- 谢谢 - 你最近怎么样？
我打算开家餐厅  卖乳酪牛排什么的
Why, Dolores? Why did you say that to him? He has the wrong idea.
你哪来的钱？
我存够钱了  放心吧
Everything's fine, Patrick. I'm more concerned about you than anything else.
你赌球赚的钱？
- 谁跟你说的？- 妈妈在外面跟我说的
Good, Dad. Good.
我可没说
Okay, the question, the big question, is what are you gonna do with yourself?
妈  你刚刚在外面跟我说的
就在5分钟前我们上楼的时候
What am I gonna do? I'm getting in shape, I'm getting trim,
你说别多嘴  你爸丢了工作  现在在赌球
I'm getting really fit for Nikki. I'm gonna read Nikki's teaching
syllabus and get my old job back.
多洛蕾丝  干嘛要跟他说  他理解错了
没事  帕特里克  我最担心的是你
Nikki sold the house. She left. Didn't your mother tell you that?
我很好  爸爸  很好
现在最大的问题是  你有什么打算？
Let me tell you something. You don't know anything about my marriage, okay, Dad?
我的打算？ 我要减肥
All right? Our marriage... we're very, very much in love,
能配得上尼基  还要读完尼基教学大纲的书
okay? Just like you two.
Listen, Patrick, she's gone. She's not around anymore. Nikki left.
回去工作
What are you doing, Dad? You know what? Excelsior. Excelsior. What does that mean?
她把房子卖了  她走了
It means you know what I'm gonna do, I'm gonna take all this
你妈没告诉你吗？
听我说  你根本不了解我的婚姻
negativity and use it as fuel and I'm gonna find a silver lining,
我们的婚姻…我们感情很好
that's what I'm gonna do. And that's no bullshit.
就像你们俩一样
That's no bullshit. That takes work and that's the truth.
帕特里克  她搬走了  不住这附近了
爸  你想干什么  我会精进不休
- 精进不休 - 什么意思？
你知道吗  我会承受所有的不愉快
化之为动力  拨开乌云  发现一丝幸福线
我说到做到  绝不是胡扯
这不是胡扯  我会为之努力  我会把它实现
What the fuck?!
Stupid fucking book!
I just can't believe Nikki's teaching that book to the kids.
I mean the whole time -let me just break it down for you
- the whole time you're rooting for this Hemingway guy to survive the war
and to be with the woman that he loves, Catherine Barkley...
It's four o'clock in the morning, Pat.
... and he does. He does. He survives the war, after getting
搞什么啊？！
blown up he survives it, and he escapes to Switzerland with
Catherine. But now Catherine's pregnant. Isn't that wonderful?
「永别了  武器」
这是什么该死的破书！
She's pregnant. And they escape up into the mountains and they're
真不敢相信尼基居然让学生看这种书
gonna be happy, and they're gonna be drinking wine and they dance --
我是说  自始至终…听我慢慢说
they both like to dance with each other, there's scenes of them
你一直盼着海明威笔下这个人能从战争中挺过来
dancing, which was boring, but I liked it, because they were happy.
跟他爱的凯瑟琳・巴克利在一起…
You think he ends it there? No! He writes another ending.
帕特  现在才凌晨4点
She dies, Dad! I mean, the world's hard
他办到了  他真的办到了  他挺过来了
他挨了一炮居然挺过来了
enough as it is, guys. It's fucking hard enough as it is.
带着凯瑟琳逃到瑞士
Can't somebody say, Hey, let's be positive?
就在这时凯瑟琳怀孕了  这不是好事吗？
Let's have a good ending to the story??
她怀孕了  他们逃到了山里
他们会很幸福  一起喝酒  一起跳舞
Pat, you owe us an apology.
他们喜欢一起跳舞  有好几场呢
Mom, for what, I can't apologize.
读起来很烦  但我喜欢  因为他们很幸福
I'm not gonna apologize for this.
You know what I will do? I will apologize on behalf of
你以为这就完了？ 没完！
Ernest Hemingway, because that's who's to blame here.
他写了另一种结局
Yeah, have Ernest Hemingway call us and apologize to us, too.
她死了  爸爸
我是说  这个世界已经够残忍了
该死的已经够残忍了
难道就不能来点积极的吗？
故事就不能有个美满结局吗？
Why didn't you run with me? Huh!!
帕特  你该向我们道歉
I was reading.
妈  凭什么  我不会道歉的
Please. Do us a favor, don't read for a while.
我不会为这件事道歉
What are you wearing a garbage bag for? I'm gonna go run now.
知道吗  该道歉的是欧内斯特・海明威
Wait, wait, wait. You have to fix this window.
这都是他的错
I'll fix it when I get back. Fix it now.
那就让海明威也打电话给我们道歉
Get in the car, Pat. You have to go to therapy.
I don't wanna go to therapy.
You have to go. It's part of the deal. You can't live with us and not go.
你怎么不跟我一起跑步？
我要看书
行行好  少看点书吧
- 你套个垃圾袋干嘛？ - 我要去跑步
等等  你得先把窗户修好
- 我回来再修 - 现在就修
上车  帕特  该去看心理医生了
我不想去看心理医生
你非去不可  说好的  不然就别想住这
Is that song really playing?
We have music sometimes.
That song is killing me. Could you please turn it off?
I can't.
What do you mean, you can't?
I don't have the controls. I'm sorry, I-
Did Doctor Timbers put you up to this?
Is there a speaker here?
Is, is the speaker here?
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. Okay... I'm sorry.
I'll fix all this, okay?
是你放的那首歌吗？
我们偶尔会放音乐
我受不了  能关掉吗？
That was a messed up thing you did, Doctor Patel. Alright!
不能
That's a messed up thing. I'm sorry, but that's... .
什么叫不能？
You can call me Cliff, please.
遥控器不在我这里  很抱歉…
Yeah, well, Cliff, that's not the way you're supposed to meet people, okay?
廷伯斯医生叫你这么做的？
You should write that down in your, I don't know
扬声器在哪儿？
your little book you write stuff down in.
I'm sorry about that song. I just wanted to see if it was still a trigger for you.
Bravo. It's a trigger. I'm not gonna take any meds,
对不起  真对不起
我会把这些都放好  好吗？
I should just tell you that right now.
No, You have to take medicine.
No, I'm not gonna take any medicine. It makes me foggy-
No, you will have to take medication.
I don't want any meds, Doctor.
Look, I am not the explosion guy, okay? My father is the explosion guy.
你把事情搞得一团糟  帕特尔医生
真是一团糟  我很抱歉
你可以叫我克里夫
I'm not that guy.
好吧  克里夫  你这么做是不对的
He got kicked out of that stadium he beat up so many people at Eagles games, he's on the exclusion list.
你应该把这个记在那什么上面
I had one incident. One incident can change a lifetime.
记在你的小本子上
放那首歌是我不对  我只想看是否还会刺激你
好极了  还是有反应
But I'm ready. I'm ready to take responsibility for my side of the street.
不过我什么药也不会吃
She just needs to take responsibility for hers.
先跟你讲明了
你必须得吃药
What's hers?
我什么药都不会吃  一吃药我就头昏
What's hers? Are you joking? Let's go back to the incident.
你非吃药不可
我什么药都不想吃
我不爱乱发火的
I come home from work after I..
爱发火的是我爸
不是我
fight with Nancy, the high school ... principal.
他在老鹰队的比赛上打了好几次架
I come home and what's playing but the song from my wedding.
被赶出了球场  上了黑名单
The song that you so charmingly played out here today for us.
- 我只出过一次事 - 一次就够了
That's playing and I don't think anything of it. Which is odd,
cause I should have.
I come home, what do I see? I walk in the door and I see underwear and
可我已经准备好了  我准备负我的责任
pieces of clothing and a guy's pants with his belt in it,
她也得负她的责任
and I walk up the stairs, and all...
她有什么责任？
... ll of a sudden I see the DVD player, and on the D-...
她有什么责任  开什么玩笑？
... -VD player is the CD and it's playing our wedding song,
and then I look down and I see my wife's...
... panties on the ground and then-
我再给你讲讲是怎么回事
... I look up and I see her naked in the shower...
... and I think, Oh, that's kinda sweet, she's in the shower.
我上班中途回家  我一般不这样
What a perfect thing. I'm gonna find her and maybe I'll go in there.
We never-... ... fuck in the shower anymore.
但那天我跟校长吵了一架
Maybe today we will. ?I...
我回到家  家里正在放我婚礼上的那首歌
... pull the curtain back and there's the fucking history...
就是你今天放的那首
... -teacher with tenure.
我听到了也没多想
And you know what he says to me? You should probably go. ?
我要是想想就好了
然后呢  我进了门  看见满地的衣物
That's what he says to me.
其中还有条男裤  皮带还系在上面
So yeah, I snapped. I almost beat him to death. But now I get fucking
我一上楼
chastised for it? I'm parallel to my father? I don't think so.
就看见DVD播放器里面有张CD
正在放那首歌
All right. Can you talk about something that you did, before or after?
然后  我一低头就看见了地上
我老婆的内裤
抬头一看  她光着身子在洗澡
Yeah, about a week before the incident, I called the cops and
我就想  天哪  她在洗澡  真迷人
I told them that my wife and the history guy were plotting against
天赐良机  我干嘛不进去
me by embezzling money from the local high school, which
我们好久没在浴室做了
说不定今天可以试试
我拉开浴帘  那个该死的历史老师…
正忙活着呢
wasn't true...It was a delusion. And we later found out from the hospital
你知道他怎么说吗
that's because I'm, uh...
你还是回避一下吧
... undiagnosed bipolar.
他就是这么说的
然后我就爆发了  差点把他打死
Yeah. With mood swings and weird thinking brought on by severe
可我凭什么因为这个受罚？
我跟我爸一样了吗？
stress, which rarely happens, thank God.
我可不觉得
好吧  能讲讲那前后发生了什么吗？
And then the shower incident happened and that's when everything
那件事发生一个礼拜前  我报了警
snapped, so I then realized that, oh, wow, I've been dealing with
说我老婆跟那个历史老师背着我
this my whole life. And without any supervision I've been doing it all
贪污学校的钱
on my own with no help and basically I've been white-knuckling it this whole time.
其实没这回事  是我幻想出来的
后来  我们去了医院
That had to be hard.
发现原来我有…
Yeah. It's a lot to deal with, especially when you don't know what the hell is happening,
双向情感障碍症
which I do now. Sort of.
是的  情绪波动很大
Pat, you have to take your medication.
I can't, Mom. I can't.
压力作用下还会妄想
I will call them. They'll come for you.
幸好不常发作
Why would you do that? You wouldn't do that. Why would you call them?
What's up?
I don't, I don't feel good when I'm on them, Mom. I don't feel good.
然后浴室事件发生了  一切就这么爆发了
I'm so much clearer without them. Mom, they make me bloated.
I don't like the way it makes me look.
我才意识到原来我一直被这种毛病困扰着
You've gotta take your medication.
Why don't you just take your medication?
Come on, I'm doing it with my physicality. I've been workin' out,
而且还一直无人帮忙  只能独自面对
that's what I'm doin'.
Why is he wearing a garbage bag?
Why are you wearing a garbage bag?
成天紧张得指关节发白
To sweat.
Sit down. We're seven minutes in, no score. Come on, help turn the juju around.
I don't believe in juju, Dad.
难为你了
Come on, Mister Excelsior. You wanna be positive? Be positive. Sit down.
是的  真的很难
All right, all right.
尤其是当你不知道怎么回事的时候
Come on.
虽然我现在大概知道了
For a second. I'll watch the beginning of the game.
He says you're good.... . luck, honey.
帕特  你得吃药
What's that in your hand?
It's a... see?
我没法吃  妈
那我就给他们打电话  让他们把你带走
Handkerchief? Yeah.
你怎么会那么做  你不会的
你怎么会去找他们
怎么了？
妈  我吃了药会不舒服
真的不舒服
我不吃药的话清醒得多  药还会让我发胖
That's OCD. That's crazy.
我不想胖成那样
What OCD? I want my son to watch the game with me, so sue me.
你把药吃了不就行了吗？
你必须得吃药
Just sit down, come on. I want you to watch the game with me.
拜托  就不能运动吗  我一直在健身
I'm not superstitious. That's a small thing that I do.
现在正准备去呢
他干嘛要套个垃圾袋在身上？
你干嘛要套个垃圾袋在身上？
If I make a lot of money, what's the difference if I do this or that?
更容易出汗
坐下来  我们0比7落后呢
It's a small thing. Sit down. Come on.
来帮我把运气转回来
I'm making crabby snacks and homemades.
爸  我可不信什么运气
得了  精进不休先生
You see?! You see that?! You're meant to be here!
你不是想积极吗  过来坐下
来吧
就看一会儿  看完开局我就走
This is special. Everything happens for a reason.
他说你是福星呢  儿子
That's why you came home. Embrace it! Embrace it!
你手里拿着什么？
是个…看见没有？
I'm the reason? I don't think so.
Yeah, Tommy, Tommy, yes, yes. I got your whole sheet.
Mom. Yeah. No, no...
- 手帕？ - 嗯
... I'm just confirming.
I'm just confirming. Okay.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Can I do. . an interview for a school project on mental illness? No.
强迫症  疯子
It's for a school project! Don't pay any attention.
我只想让儿子陪我看球  有错吗？
Who's that? That's not Rick D'Angelo, is it? That's him.
坐下来  我只是想让你陪我看场球
Is he the guy who's having the problem?
People are stupid. They, they, they, they don't know what they're saying.
我这不是迷信  不过是个小嗜好而已
Yeah, that's the one.
Don't let them hurt your feelings.
Pat, don't look for Nikki! Take your camera and get out of here!
只要能赚到钱  怎么赚的又有什么关系？
Patrick, please. Pat!
小嗜好而已嘛  快坐下
Patty! Don't look for Nikki!
我在做小点心
你懂了吗  这是注定的！
这个球很特别  它是因为你才进的
这就是你回家的价值  承认吧！
因为我？ 我可不觉得
是的  汤米  我知道了
- 妈 - 对  不…
我只是在确认
我只是在确认  好
我来  我来
我论文选题是关于精神疾病  能做个采访吗？
Ms. Meckers!
不行
Oh, God! Oh, God!
- 是为了写论文 - 别放在心上
Nance! This is my lucky day! Look at you working on a Sunday!
- 是里克・德・安杰洛吧？- 就是他
他才有病吧？
How are you? Hey.
那些人都有病  说的都是胡话
What are you doing here?
没错  是他
犯不着为他们受气
I just came by to say hi, to let you know I'm ready to come back to work.
- 帕特  别去找尼基！- 拿上你的相机  滚！
You shouldn't be here.
I'll work full-time, half-time.
帕特里克  回来！
I'll sub, I'll work history, whatever you want.
帕特  别去找尼基！
Here, let me give you a hand. I'm sorry. I'm being rude.
I got it. I got it. I got it.
Let me ask you something. Let me just ask you something.
Does Nikki still work here?
You know I can't tell you that. But Doug Culpepper is still here.
Why would you tell me that? You know he broke up my marriage.
What, are you being, a troublemaker?
You know, you look good. Did you lose a lot of weight?
I did, yeah. I did. Thank you.
Get away from me! Get away!
I'm better. I just want to let you know, I'm better now. Okay?
I'm better. I feel good. I feel so good. Look at my eyes.
Look at my eyes. Look at how clear they are.
梅克尔女士！
I'm not a complainer anymore. I'm a positive guy. Okay?
天哪！
南希  我运气真好！
You just have to give it some time.
你居然星期天还来上班了！
Yes.
你好吗？
You know, a lot went down. People will get over it.
你跑来干嘛？
It'll be all good. It'll work out.
Yes! It will be!
我只是过来打个招呼
I'm gonna take that as a silver development, Nancy!
A silver development! That's a silver lining!
顺便跟你说  我准备回来工作了
Good luck.
你不该来的
我干全职也行  兼职也行
代课也行  教历史也行  随便你
Ronnie! Pat.
我帮你  不好意思  我吓到你了
我问你件事  就问一句
There he is! He's back!
尼基还在这上班吗？
我不能告诉你  不过道格・卡尔佩珀还在
Hey.
干嘛告诉我  你明知道他拆散了我们
Welcome home.
你这是找茬吗？
Thank you.
Welcome back, man.
Yeah, I'm out.
你气色不错  瘦了吗？
Yeah? You're out out?
Uh-huh.
Cool, man. Wow, you lost a lot of weight. I almost didn't recognize you.
没错  我是瘦了  谢谢
Thank you.
走开  离我远点！
I'm sorry I didn't visit you in the hospital. You know, work's out of
control, you know, she had the baby. I'm really glad you're back.
我只是想让你知道  我已经好了
I missed you. I really need someone to talk to. You gotta come see the baby.
我再好不过了  看我的眼睛
看我的眼睛  看我的眼神多清醒
She's beautiful. And Veronica wants to make dinner for you.
我再也不会抱怨了  变得很乐观了
Congratulations on the baby, but I'm not buying the invitation.
你只要花点时间就好
好
很多人都出过问题  但总会克服的
都会没事的  会好起来的
'Cause you think Veronica still hates you?
没错  一定会的！
乌云会慢慢散开的  南希！
会散开的  背后就是一道幸福线！
I know Veronica still hates me. That's not true.
祝你好运
Yes, it is. Nikki always said that
Ronnie's wife keeps his social calendar where she keeps his balls, in her purse. ?
罗尼  我是帕特
That's not true.
Ronnie! What are you doing?
Okay, it's a little true. But if you think she still hates you,
是他  他回来了！
you're wrong because why would she tell me to invite you to dinner?
你好
欢迎回来
Hmm?
谢谢
Did you invite him?
欢迎回来啊  老兄
Yes.
是啊  我出院了
Well, can he make it?
是吗  你出院了？
I don't know yet!  Can you
对
太棒了  你瘦了  我差点没认出来
make it next Sunday?
谢谢
很抱歉我没能去医院看你
Sure.
没办法  工作一团糟
I'll see you next Sunday.
她刚生了宝宝  你能回来我真的很高兴
Now, you guys are still in touch with Nikki, right?
我很惦记你  真想跟你好好聊聊
Does Veronica still talk to Nikki?
Yeah.
你一定要来看看我女儿
Get in here, please. I need you.
她可漂亮了  维罗妮卡想请你来吃晚餐
Okay.
恭喜你当爸爸了  不过晚餐还是算了吧
As soon as you left, the Redskins threw a trick play, a pitch out to Randal El.
Andy Reid wastes a timeout challenging it, loses the challenge, loses the game.
难道你觉得维罗妮卡还是对你有成见？
You're in this house, please show some respect for what I do.
- 我知道她一直对我有成见 - 没这回事
就是这样的  尼基以前总说
And we should spend time together anyway. I'm trying to keep you out of trouble, please.
I have very, good news, everybody. Very good news.
罗尼就是个妻管严  老婆指东他绝不敢往西
What's that? What's the good news?
没这回事
Things are looking up.
罗尼  你在干嘛？
好吧  我承认有点
Oh, are they?
不过你要是还以为她讨厌你
You know what, I knew why they invited me over. I knew it.
那就错了  要不然她干嘛请你来吃晚餐？
Listen, she might be with that guy.
你邀请他没有？
That, the... .
请了
Oh, no way!
那他能来吗？
She--, no, she might be with him. She's afraid of you.
还不知道！
She doesn't want to talk to you.
下个星期天行吗？
No way, Dad. You mean, Doug Culpepper?
Put the phone down. You gotta...
行
Wait just a minute.
下个星期天见
... Put the phone down, please.
What are you doing?
你们能联系上尼基吧？
Listen--, stop.
维罗妮卡跟尼基还有来往吗？
有
Pat!
快进屋  我找你有事
You gotta understand me. You wanna go back? Well then, stop this!
Then don't fucking do this.
好
Don't talk to me like that.
Well then, don't behave this way.
你一走  那帮印第安人就耍了个花招
I got... a call asking to...
... check on this house. Pat
安迪・瑞德浪费了一次暂停
Solatano?
Yeah.
失去了反击机会  输了比赛
Yeah? Missus Solatano, Mister Solatano, I'm Officer Keogh.
I work this beat. Look, I heard about the restraining order.
你既然住在这  好歹尊重一下我的事情
And I heard you went to your old house and the school.
至少陪陪我
It's not okay. I've been assigned to your case, so you're
我只是不想让你惹麻烦
gonna be seeing a lot of me. Do yourself a favor. Respect the restraining order, okay?
我有个天大的好消息要告诉你们
Five hundred feet. You hear what he just said? Youhave a restraining order.
什么好消息？
事情有转机了
Yeah, Dad, I know.
是吗？
Thank you, Officer.
我就知道他们为什么邀请我  我就知道
If you need anything... my card.
Thank you. Sorry. We understand.
听着  她可能跟那个家伙在一起了
Since when do cops have cards?
这…
不可能！
她可能会和他在一起  她怕你
不想跟你说话
不可能  爸  你是说道格・卡尔佩珀吗？
Tell me one thing. Would you like to be a guy who goes back to jail
把电话放下  你会…
等一下
or to the hospital? Hmm? So take your medication and if you do fine,
把电话放下
你这是干什么？
听着  别打
- 把电话给我 - 爸  这是我自己的事情
we'll reduce them.
把电话给我  把电话给我
Nikki's waiting for me to get in shape and get my life in order, and
帕特！
我这是为你好  别这么做！
then she's gonna be with me. And that's better than any medication.
别做这种蠢事
别讲这种话
Pat, there's a possibility, and I want you to be prepared for it,
那你就别做这种事啊
我接到一个电话
that she may not return. True love is about letting her go and seeing
要求检查一下这座房子
帕特・索拉塔诺？
我是
if she returns. In the meantime, if you listen to that song, I don't
索拉塔诺夫人  索拉塔诺先生  我是基奥警官
负责这片辖区  据我所知  你有人身限制令
want you to fall apart. So get a strategy, okay? You need one.
我听说你去了过去的房子  还有学校
这是不允许的  你的案子分给我来管
Let me say something, I gotta say something.
所以你以后会经常见到我  好自为之
Okay.
拿限制令当回事  好吧？
This is what I believe to be true.
This is what I learned in the hospital.
- 五百英尺以内 - 听到没有？
You have to do everything you can, you have to work your
你有人身限制令呢
hardest, and if you do, if you stay positive,
爸  我知道
谢谢你  警官
you have a shot at a silver lining.
有什么需要的话  这是我的名片
谢谢你  不好意思  我们知道了
警察什么时候开始印名片了？
Work on a strategy, okay?
Hey, my friend Ronnie's having this party on Sunday night and it's like
我问你  你是想回去坐牢
a real hoity-toity thing and his wife, Veronica's a real stickler for... .
还是想回医院  老老实实吃药
I don't know, my mom got this Gap outfit she wants me to wear, but I wanna wear a jersey
等你好了  就不用吃了
that my brother, Jake, got me from the Eagles.
尼基在等我康复  等我重振旗鼓
Which jersey?
那时候她就会回到我身边  这比什么药都管用
DeSean Jackson.
DeSean Jackson is the man.
帕特  那只是一种可能  可你也得有心理准备
Well, that settles that.
她可能不会回来了
如果你真的爱她  就该让她走
等她自己决定是否回来
另外  如果听到那首歌
Pat! What are you doin'?
我希望你不要再崩溃了  想个对策  这很有必要
I gotta go, man.
我有话要说
Why?
行
I can't stay, come on. I made a mistake, I shouldn't have worn this.
这是我的信条
Dude, you're fine. I like that jersey. I wish I was wearing that jersey.
这是我在医院里所学到的
I feel like an idiot.
你要竭尽你所能  尽你最大的努力
Are you comfortable?
Veronica's not gonna like it.
只要你努力了  只要你始终积极向上
Get over here.
Plus you got a tie on.
Don't worry about it, you're the guest of honor. You come however you wanna come.
Really?
你就能从乌云背后看到一丝幸福线
Get over here.
DeSean Jackson's in the house!
还是想想对策  好吗？
You mean rookie of the year?
Yeah.
DeSean Jackson? DeSean Jackson?
我朋友罗尼星期天晚上有个聚会
Oh, you wore a jersey to dinner.
Isn't it awesome?
是那种正式晚宴
Not for dinner.
他老婆维罗妮卡又很讲究…
Look, he got us flowers.
我妈找了套西装让我穿
Oh, that's sweet. That's sweet, Pat. That's lovely.
可我想穿件球衣
And wine.
是我哥杰克送我的老鹰队球衣
Hey.
谁的球衣？
Check this out. We just redid the whole thing.
Wow!
德肖恩・杰克逊
Tremendous. Tremendous.
德肖恩・杰克逊是条汉子
Isn't it great?
Tremendous.
那就这么定了
Yeah, man, I'm, I'm thinking of redoing it again.
Why?
Because. Gotta be making a lot of paper to do that.
Yeah, we're doing all right, man. I can't complain.
Isn't the market down, though?
It is down, but you know, she wants more, so I'm giving her more, man.
Hey, you know my dad lost his pension.
帕特  你怎么了？
I'm sorry, man.
Yeah.
A lot of people. My uncle, too.
Really?
我得走了
Yeah, but you know what? No disrespect, it's not personal,
but this is the time to strike.
为什么？
我不能留下来  我错了  不该穿成这样
You start snapping up commercial real estate -- cheap -- flip it
没事  那件球衣挺好的  我都想穿了
over, you flip it over and that's when you make the money.
我觉得蠢死了
But the pressure... it's like... .
你不自在吗？
维罗妮卡会不喜欢的
过来吧
你还系了领带呢
别担心了  你可是贵客
想怎么样就怎么样
You okay?
真的吗？
来吧
I'm not okay. Don't tell anybody. Listen to me.
德肖恩・杰克逊大驾光临！
你是说那个年度最佳新球员？
I feel like I'm getting crushed and-
就是他
德肖恩・杰克逊  德肖恩・杰克逊
Crushed by what?
天  你居然穿件球衣来宴会
Everything. The family, the baby, the job, the fucking dicks at work,
很酷吧
and it's like, you know, like I'm trying to do this, you know, and,
不太合时宜
他还带了花来呢
真漂亮  帕特  你真有心
and, and I'm like... suffocating.
Holy shit.
好啊
来看看吧  我们刚刚重新装修过
You can't be happy all the time.
Who told you you can't be happy?
太棒了  太棒了
It's all right. You just do your best, you have no choice.
不错吧？
太棒了
That's not true at all. You just can't.
我还想再装修一次
为什么？
- 因为… - 那可得花不少钱呢
Ronnie, Ronnie, Ronnie!
我们付得起  没得说的
I hope you're okay with Veronica's sister coming over.
经济不是不景气吗？
You okay with that? Who?
是不景气  可她想要什么我就得满足她
Veronica's sister.
我爸失去了养老金了
Tiffany. Tiffany and... Tommy?
我很遗憾
Yeah. Just Tiffany.
很多人都这样  我叔父也是
What happened to Tommy?
是吗？
He died.
是  不过你知道吗  我不是在说你爸
Tommy died? Cops die.
现在正是罢工的好时机
How'd he die?
你可以开始抢购商品房
Please, don't bring it up.
趁现在便宜  到处都在抛售
No, how did he die?
How did who die?
然后你再转手抛出去  就能赚到差价
Hey, Tiffany! This is Pat. Pat, my sister-in-law Tiffany.
但这个压力…实在是…
你还好吧？
You look nice.
我不太好  别跟人说
Thank you.
I'm not flirting with you.
我感觉自己快被压碎了
Oh, I didn't think you were.
I just see that you made an effort and I'm gonna be better with my
wife, I'm working on that. I wanna acknowledge her beauty.
什么事？
家庭、孩子、工作、混账同事  所有这些
I never used to do that. I do that now.
Cause we're gonna be better than ever... Nikki. Just practicing.
我觉得自己像是这样…
How'd Tommy die?
都快要窒息了
What about your job?
天哪
人没办法一直保持那么快乐
I just got fired, actually.
谁说不能？
Oh, really? How?
是这样的  你只能尽力而为  别无选择
I mean, I'm sorry. How'd that happen?
Does it really matter?
- 不是这样的 - 真的不行
罗尼  罗尼！
Baby, how's it going?
维罗妮卡的妹妹也要过来  别介意
Great, great.
- 你不介意吧？ - 谁啊？
维罗妮卡的妹妹
- 蒂芙尼 - 蒂芙尼和…汤米？
只有蒂芙尼过来
汤米怎么了？
We're gonna go on a tour now.
他死了
Let's go see the house.
- 汤米死了？ - 警察总是活不长
Come on, let's go for the tour.
他怎么死的？
I've, I've been planning this forever. I love our house.
拜托  别提这事儿
他怎么死的？
I love our house. I'm really excited about it.
谁怎么死的？
Come on.
蒂芙尼  这是帕特  帕特  这是我妻妹
Guess what it is.
Oh, it's a television. It's a computer screen. Nope.
Just keep going, keep going, keep going.
It's a brick oven, it's a brick oven. It's a light. It's a...
你看上去很漂亮
Ooh, ooh, warmer, warmer, warmer.
谢谢
... it's a drawer at a morgue where they pull out dead
我这不是在调戏你
bodies and shoot them with formaldehyde. Where would the body go, though?
我也没那么觉得
It's a joke!
我看得出来你用心打扮了  我想跟我妻子和好
It's a... fireplace.
正在为之努力  我要学会夸赞她的美貌
In the middle of the wall?
我以前从不这么做  现在要学着做了
We have a port in every room. Gimme an iPod.
这样我们就能和好  为了尼基练习一下而已
Who, who doesn't have an iPod?
汤米怎么死的？
Well, I don't have an iPod. I don't even have a phone.
They won't let me make any calls. They think I'm gonna call Nikki.
工作还顺利吗？
Don't worry about it. Don't focus on that.
我刚被炒了
I would call Nikki.
天哪  真的吗  怎么炒的？
I'm actually gonna give you one of my iPods. I have an old one.
不好意思  我是说  怎么回事？
Gimme your iPod.
这还重要吗？
Give it to me. Thank you, baby, thank you.
Of all the rooms there are iPod ports in,
亲爱的  你们好吗？
I'm happy you brought us into the bathroom.
很好  很好
I can play music for the baby in any room.
Can you play Ride the Lightning?by Metallica?
Pat was a history sub at the high school, Tiffany.
Ask him about any president, he knows 'em all.
带他们到处转转吧
咱们去参观房子吧
Here's a fun fact. You know where the term OK?comes from?
走吧  带你们转转
我筹划好久了  我爱我们的房子
No. No, I don't.
我爱我们的房子  我实在太兴奋了
Where?
走吧
Well, Martin Van Buren, the eighth president of the United States of
America, is from Kinderhook, New York...
猜猜这是干什么用的
Oh.
- 电视机 - 电脑屏 - 都不对
... and he was part of a club, a men's club, called Old Kinderhook.
继续猜  继续猜
And if you were cool, you were in the club, they'd say,
- 是个砖灶 - 是个壁灯
That guy's OK. ? Cause he was in the Old Kinderhooks.
再想想
是停尸房抽屉  从里面把尸体拖出来
注射福尔马林  然后要把尸体放在哪？
Really?
Yeah. Pretty cool, right?
我说着玩的！
That's interesting.
这是个壁炉
You know, Tiffany's been doing this dance thing for years and she's
real good at it. She's gonna be competing at the Ben Franklin Hotel.
在墙中间？
Oh, really? My wife loves dance. Nikki loves dance.
我们每个房间都有接口  给我个iPod
Why do you have to talk about me like that?
谁会没有iPod啊？
I'm just bragging about you. Can't I brag about my little sister?
Don't talk about me in the third person.
我就没有  我连手机也没有
Please, gimme a break.
他们不准我打电话  怕我打给尼基
I'm right here.
别想这个了
Just be nice. Just be nice.
Wow, wow, wow. Fascinating.
我是会打给尼基的
Sorry. I don't wanna be mean.
我送个iPod给你吧
I know. I know, I know.
我有个旧的
把你的iPod给我
What meds are you on?
给我  谢谢
既然那么多房间都有iPod接口
Me? None. I used to be on Lithium and Seroquel and Abilify,
你干嘛偏偏带我们来洗手间看这个
不管在哪个房间  我都能给宝宝放音乐
but I don't take them anymore, no. They make me foggy
能放金属乐队的《乘着闪电》吗？
and they also make me bloated.
Yeah, I was on Xanax and Effexor, but I agree, I wasn't as sharp,
蒂芙尼  帕特以前在高中当历史老师
so I stopped. You ever take Klonopin?
随便挑任总统问他  他能给你如数家珍
Klonopin?  Yeah.
给你们讲个好玩的
Right? Jesus.
你们知道“OK”这个词怎么来的吗？
It's like, What? What day is it?? How about Trazodone?
不知道
Trazodone!
怎么来的？
Oh, it flattens you out. I mean, you are done.
马丁・范步伦  美国第八任总统
It takes the light right out of your eyes.
纽约州肯德胡克人
God, I bet it does.
他组建了一个男性俱乐部  叫老肯德胡克
要是一个人够酷  又进了那个俱乐部
I'm tired. I wanna go.
别人就会说“那家伙OK”  因为他是老肯德胡克的
No. No, no, no, no. We haven't, we haven't even finished the salad
真的吗？
yet, or the duck. I made the Fire and Ice cake.
真的  有意思吧
有意思
蒂芙尼练过几年舞蹈
I said I'm tired. Are you gonna walk me home or what?
跳得可棒了  她要参加富兰克林酒店的比赛
是吗  我老婆也喜欢跳舞  尼基喜欢跳舞
You mean me?
你干嘛用那种口气说我的事情？
Yeah, you. Are you gonna walk me home?
我在夸你呢  我就不能夸自己的妹妹吗？
You have poor social skills. You have a problem.
别在外人面前讲我的事情
I have a problem? You say more inappropriate things than
拜托  给我个面子吧
我已经给你面子了
appropriate things. You scare people.
态度好点儿
I tell the truth. But you're mean.
好精彩
What? I'm not telling the truth?
不好意思  我也不想这么不讲理
Um, maybe I should drive them home separately?
没事儿  我知道
You can drive them both home. Now.
你用的是什么药？
我什么也没用  以前用斯瑞康和阿立派唑
Stop talking about me in third person. You can take Tiffany home first.
You love it when I have problems.
不过现在不吃了  吃了头晕
You love it, Von, because then you can be the good one. Just say it.
No... I don't. I don't. I just wanted to have a nice,
还会发胖
我以前用阿普唑仑和文法拉辛
I just wanted to have a nice dinner. Oh, God.
不过头脑确实糊涂
What is your problem?!
- 我就没再用了 - 用过氯硝西泮吗？
Nothing's my problem! I'm fine. I'm tired and I wanna go.
氯硝西泮？ 用过
Come on, are you ready?
- 对吧？ - 天哪
You really, you really wanna go right now?
感觉就好像  今天礼拜几来着
Yes, I really wanna go! It's been great.
- 曲唑酮呢？- 曲唑酮！
Okay, guys, the baby is sleeping!
Sorry. I don't wanna wake up the baby. Bye.
那玩意真能把人放倒  吃了就像死人一样
两眼无光
天  肯定是的
我累了  我要走了
不行  我们连沙拉都还没吃完
鸭肉也没吃  我还做了冰淇淋呢
Listen, I haven't dated since before my marriage so I don't
我说我累了  你送不送我回家？
really remember how this works.
How what works?
你问我？
I saw the way you were looking at me, Pat.
就是你  送我回家吗？
You felt it, I felt it, don't lie. We're not liars like they are.
你完全不通人情  情商很有问题
I live in the addition around back, which is completely
我情商有问题？ 你说的明明比我还不得体
separate from my parents' house, so there's no chance of them walking
根本不顾别人感受
in on us. I hate the fact that you wore a football jersey to dinner
我那叫坦诚  你这叫不讲理
什么  我怎么不讲理了？
because I hate football, but you can fuck me if you turn the lights off, okay?
要不我把你俩各自送回家？
你可以把他俩一起送回家  现在就送
How old are you?
- 少在外人面前说我 - 先送蒂芙尼
Old enough to have a marriage end and not wind up in a mental hospital.
你可喜欢看我出糗了
你可喜欢了  让你有种优越感  对吧
Look, I had a really good time tonight and I think you're really
没有  没有  我只是想…
pretty, but I'm married, okay?
- 只是想好好吃顿饭 - 天哪
你到底哪里不满意？
You're married? So am I.
我没什么不满意  我只是累了  想回家
你走吗？
你真的现在就要走吗？
没错  我真的要走了  感谢你们的盛情款待
No, that's confusing. He's dead.
拜托  轻点儿  宝宝睡了！
不好意思  我不是有意要吵醒宝宝的  再见
Wait, what?
What's happening?
Oh, my God. Hey.
我结婚以后就没有约会过了
所以不记得这事儿有什么规矩了
什么事？
我瞧见你色迷迷的眼神了  帕特
你我都有感觉  别不承认  我们不是那些伪君子
我住在后院的小楼里
Are you okay? Ronnie called. Hey, is that make-up on your shirt?
跟我父母分开住  所以我们绝对不会被他们撞见
I don't know, Mom.
我很讨厌你穿件球衣去晚宴
What happened over there?
我讨厌橄榄球  不过只要你别开灯  你可以上我
When am I gonna get a phone?
You'll get a phone in due time.
What happened?
Pat!
你多大？
大到结过婚  还混出了疯人院
虽然今晚跟你相处很愉快  而且你很漂亮
可我结婚了  懂吗？
你结婚了？ 我也是
Mom!
不  你搞错了  他死了
I can't find my wedding video. Mom, wake up.
What is it?
Where's my wedding video?
It's after three o'clock! What are you doing?
I looked in here, but this is all your sewing shit up here, for your
sewing and everything. Did you put it up here?
What about in your father's study?
慢着  怎么了？
Don't go in my study.
你怎么了？
Dad, not now!
天哪
Would you put it in here? It makes no sense for you to put it in here.
Patty, what are you doing?
He's got all his Eagles videos and not one video of my wedding!
Is it here? I mean... . ?
Patty!
It's probably in the attic.
Are you going in my study?
It feels to me like you wanna hide my wedding video.
Please stop yelling!
I'm not yelling, Mom, I'm just frustrated
because I should have my fucking wedding video!
Pat! Pat!
I looked over there! I already looked all over there!
Calm down, Pat.
I'm not calming down! I don't give a fuck who hears,
你没事吧  罗尼打电话来了
你衣服上的是化妆品吗？
I'm not calming down! Anybody can wake up!
我不知道
I'm not ashamed of it! I'm not ashamed of it!
到底出什么事了？
Let the whole neighborhood wake up! I...... don't care!
什么时候才能给我个手机？
到时候会给你的
Pat! Stop it!
怎么回事？
Stop it! Stop it! Stop it!
帕特！
What's going on?
What?
I want it! It-...
Hey!
It's my wedding! It's my wedding video!
Pat! Stop it! Stop it! Stop it!
I can't watch my wedding video, but I CAN hear the fucking song
妈！
我找不到我的婚礼录像了  醒醒
怎么了？
我的婚礼录像呢？
Mom?
才3点  你搞什么鬼？
What the fuck you doing?! You...... hit your mother?!
我在这里找了  可全是针线什么的
No, no, no, no, no!
你放在这了吗？
Stop it!
在不在你爸的书房？
Get off me, Dad!
别进我书房
Stop hitting him!
爸  别闹！
你会放在这吗？ 放这没道理啊
帕特  你要干嘛？
I'm not hitting him! He's hitting me!
这全是老鹰队的比赛录像  就是没婚礼录像！
在这吗？
I'm sorry! I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
帕特！
可能在阁楼
你进我的书房了吗？
感觉就像你故意把婚礼录像藏起来一样
Police! Open up.
别嚷了！
Mister Solatano, I got a lot of calls.
妈  我没嚷  我只是有点烦躁
People in the neighborhood are scared. I gotta come in.
因为我找不到该死的婚礼录像了!
How are we doing in here, huh?
帕特！
There are a lot of reports from your neighbors, we got a lot of phone calls.
- 我去那边找！ - 那边我找过了！
Nikki is being manipulated and controlled. You have to talk to her.
静一静  帕特
Hey, sit down.
我才不要静一静  我不管有谁听到了
Sit down.
You gotta stop with these crazy theories.
我才不要静一静  吵醒就吵醒了！
He's a cop. What are you doing?
我不觉得丢人！
It's a medication problem, but he's fine now.
Oh yeah? He's fine now? You wanna send him back to Baltimore?
整条街都醒过来吧  我才不管呢！
We know all about the explosion at the psychiatrist's office.
帕特  别嚷了！
What?
别嚷了！别嚷了！
What explosion? No. Cliff is lying, that's not true.
怎么回事？
He's not allowed to talk about that.
怎么了？
Jesus Christ, who's that?
我一定要找到！
Keep an eye on him.
那是我的婚礼  那是我的婚礼录像！
Is this a bipolar episode?
帕特  别嚷了！
Get outta here, you little fuckin'
我看不到婚礼录像  却听得到那首歌
idiot! Get outta here!
Someone, help me! Help me!
You can't tell Nikki about this,
Officer.
Look, I gotta make out a report.
No, no! No!
Hey! Sit down.
No, no, no, listen, sir.
He's chasing me! This guy's chasing me! Help me!
Sit down!
I'm sorry. I could just write you a letter and you could just
let me have five minutes, explaining how much better I'm doing.
There's a court order against you -- five hundred feet. Listen to me!
... and I'll take that fucking camera and I'm gonna break it over
your fuckin' head, then I'm gonna come back and interview you about
妈？
what it's like to get that fuckin' camera broken over your head!
你搞什么  居然敢打你妈？
不是的！
Youwa--, what are you laughing about?
别打了！
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
爸  放开我！
I'm sorry.
别打他！
Okay.
Go back to sleep. The party's over. Show's over.
别打他！
... this is not a reflection of where I'm at. You can't... please,
you can't tell her any of this You can't tell Nikki about this.
我没打他  是他在打我！
You need to pipe down.
对不起！
Everything all right?
Who was at the door?
Who was that, Dad?
It was that kid with the camera.
Good luck. I gotta write this up.
Come on, don't write it up! I don't want her to see this!
我是警察  开门
It's okay, everything is okay. We're fine, thank you,
we appreciate it. Thank you.
索拉塔诺先生  我接到不少报警
附近的人都吓坏了  我得进去
这是怎么回事？
我们接到了不少报案
尼基被人误导了  你得跟她谈谈
坐下
你别再胡说八道了
他是警察  你想干嘛？
是药物作用  不过现在没事了
是吗  还想把他送回巴尔的摩吗？
我们都知道他在心理医生那里发病了
什么？
没有  克里夫乱说的  没那回事
他没权利谈这种事
天哪  是谁？
看好他
这是双向情感障碍症的症状吗？
滚出去  你个白痴！
滚出去！
救命！
长官  你不能把这个告诉尼基
我总得写报告吧
不行  长官
坐下
那家伙在追杀我  救命！
坐下！
对不起  我可以给你写封信
或者给我几分钟  听我解释  我真的好多了
法庭对你有禁令  五百英尺  听我说！
我就把那台该死的摄像机砸在你头上
Hey!
然后再来采访你
What the hell?
被那台该死的摄像机爆头是什么滋味！
What happened to your face?
笑什么笑？
Weight lifting accident.
对不起  对不起
That sounds like bullshit. Why'd you run by my house?
对不起就完了
好吧
Did our little conversation get you upset last night?
回去睡觉  好戏演完了
Hey, this is my route, okay? Just back off.
这并不能反映我的精神状况  拜托了
This is my neighborhood. You just ran by my house.
你不能告诉她  不能告诉尼基
I like to run by myself, okay?
冷静一下
Me too.
没事吧？
Hey, I like to run alone! Will you stop?
门外是谁？
What?
爸  是谁？
Okay? I'm running here! Me too!
拿摄像机的小孩
Well then, why don't you run somewhere else?
祝你好运  我得去写报告了
There's a fucking ton of roads to run in! What are you trying to do?
拜托  别记这件事  我不想让她看见！
I like this road. This is my neighborhood.
没事  一切都很好  谢谢
Oh, come on, please!
我们能理解  谢谢你
Calm down, crazy.
Hey!
What the fuck?!
I'm married!
So am I!
What the fuck are you doing? Your husband's dead!
Where is your wife?
You're crazy!
I'm not the one that just got out of that hospital in Baltimore.
I'm not the big slut!
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I was a big slut, but I'm not anymore. There's always gonna be a
part of me that's sloppy and dirty, but I like that, with all the other
parts of myself. Can you say the same about yourself, fucker?!
Can you forgive? Are you any good at that?
搞什么鬼？
You seemed to have trouble last night.
你脸上怎么了？
Let me just set the record straight about last night.
被杠铃砸的
Hurting my mother was a mistake and I hate myself for it,
少扯了  你怎么跑到我家旁边来了？
and I hate my illness and I want to control it.
我们昨晚那场小争执惹你不爽了？
My father, on the other hand, had no trouble
这是我的线路  懂吗  别跟着我
slapping the shit out of me last night, which I did not return
我家就住附近  是你跑到我家旁边来的
cause I could've killed him and I didn't. He's sixty-five years old.
我喜欢一个人跑
You don't think I could've beat the shit out of him? I mean... .
我也是
He was scared for your mother and you hurt him as well.
我喜欢一个人跑！你就不能停下吗？
Yes, last night was a mess. Okay? And I think he probably just tried to do his best.
什么？
- 我在这条路上跑呢！ - 我也是！
你就不能换条路跑吗？
可跑的路多了去了  你安的什么心？
Pat, you have to have a strategy. I told you earlier.
我就喜欢这条路  我家就住这
You need to recognize these feelings coming to you, otherwise you will be sent
拜托  行行好！
静一静  你个疯子
back to Baltimore. So when you get these feelings, you need to get to
a quieter place, and be at peace with yourself, however you can.
Yeah, but that's easier said than done.
You have to do it. You have no choice. Excelsior.
Yeah, Excelsior. Listen, I have a letter I want you to give Nikki,
okay?
No.
Why?
Because you have a restraining
order.
What good are you, man?
Why did you have this overwhelming urgency to see your
搞什么鬼？！
我结婚了！
wedding video last night?
我也结了！
Oh, I don't know, because I'm married and I haven't seen my wife
胡扯什么呢  你丈夫已经死了！
in eight and a half months?
那你老婆又在哪儿呢？
Maybe you think that Nikki's not around and Tiffany's an attractive
你个疯子！
girl and if you get drawn towards Tiffany, you will spoil your
我又不是刚被巴尔的摩放出来
我又不是什么荡妇！
chances of getting Nikki back to you?
Not bad, Doctor Jones. But I don't think I'm gonna blow it
with Nikki because Tiffany's a slut.
对不起  对不起
Why is she a slut?
我以前确实是  可现在不是了
After the dinner at Ronnie's,
我有淫荡的一面
she said, quote, "We can go to the back house and you can fuck me as long as we turn the lights out. "
可我喜欢  和我身上其它方面一样真实
你敢这么说自己吗  色鬼？！
Unquote. And she still wears her wedding ring.
你问心无愧吗  你哪来的本钱好色？
So she's a loyal, married-to-a-dead-guy slut.
Maybe she just needs a friend and she thought if she offers you sex,
it will be easier for you to become friends with her.
你昨晚好像惹麻烦了
She said she's not a whore anymore, but she likes that part of herself
我来把昨晚的事给你讲清楚
我一时失手打了我妈  我很后悔
我恨我的疾病  我也想控制住它
along with all the other parts of herself and can I say the same?
另外  昨晚我爸把我一顿暴打
一点错也没有  我也没还手
Can you?
我怕我会失手杀了他  他已经65岁了
Is that... . ? You're asking me, you're really asking me that question?
你以为我会打不过他吗？
Yes.
他是在担心你母亲  你也打他了
With all my crazy sad shit? What, are you fucking nuts?
是的  昨晚就是一团糟
Pat, the silver lining thing is yours. I'm just giving back your
我想他也尽力了
words to you. This "crazy sad shit, " as you call it, made you a
帕特  你得有个对策  我早就告诉你了
你必须认清这些负面情绪
happier, calmer person with a beautiful positive philosophy of
不然就会被送回巴尔的摩
一旦你感觉到这些  就赶紧找个僻静地方
going outdoors, working out, and reading books.
想尽办法冷静下来
No, not the books. You said Nikki's friends with
说得倒容易
Ronnie, Veronica and Tiffany. So if you become friends with Tiffany,
你必须得做到  别无选择  精进不休
Nikki will think that you're a kind, generous, large-hearted
是啊  我给尼基写了封信  你交给她好吗？
person, who helps people in need, who is basically thriving. So if
不行
为什么？
you help Tiffany, it will be good for you.
因为你有人身限制令
你何必呢？
你昨晚为什么那么急迫地…
要看婚礼录像？
不知道  大概是因为我明明结婚了
却八个半月见不着老婆？
会不会是因为尼基不在  蒂芙尼又很迷人
万一你跟蒂芙尼有了什么瓜葛
尼基就不可能回到你身边了？
分析的不坏  琼斯博士
但我是不会放弃尼基
Hey!
因为蒂芙尼就是个荡妇
How do you know when I run?
为什么说她是个荡妇？
I wanted to clarify something.
在罗尼家吃完晚餐后
她说  我们可以到后院的小屋去
I just want us to be friends.
只要关上灯你就可以上我
Did you hear what I said?
Why are you giving me such a hard time?
这可是她的原话  她还戴着婚戒呢
所以说  她就是个对亡夫三心二意的荡妇
No, I'm not giving you a hard time.
也许她只是想交个朋友  她以为只要跟你上床
I don't know how to act with you when you do this shit.
你就会愿意跟她交朋友
You wanna have dinner at this diner?
她还说她已经不再是个荡妇了
但她喜欢自己淫荡的那一面
Pick me up at seven thirty.
因为那和她身上其方他面一样真实
还问我敢不敢这么说自己
你敢吗？
你…你是真的要我回答吗？
是的
我疯狂的那一面？你有病吗？
帕特  一丝幸福线那套理论是你发明的
我只是把那些话返还给你
正是你所说的“疯狂”的那一面
让你更加乐观镇定  有一个积极的人生观
走出家门  出去工作  读点书
不  我可不想再看书了
尼基跟罗尼  维罗妮卡和蒂芙尼是朋友
如果你跟蒂芙尼成了朋友
尼基就会觉得你是个宽厚善良的好人
Happy Halloween.
愿意伸出援手  解救迷途之人
Hi.
所以说  帮助蒂芙尼对你有好处
Here you go.
Thank you.
I'm gonna have a bowl of your Raisin Bran.
Great!
Tea Be right back.
你怎么知道我来了？
我想跟你解释一下
我只是想跟你交个朋友
You look nice.
听见没有？
Thanks.
你为什么要跟我过不去？
Raisin Bran. Milk.
我没跟你过不去
Thank you.
你这样犯浑的时候  我真不知道该怎么办
在这家餐厅吃个晚餐怎么样？
七点半来接我
You want to share this?
Why did you order Raisin Bran?
Why did you order tea?
Because you ordered Raisin Bran.
I ordered Raisin Bran because I didn't want there to be any
mistaking this for a date.
It can still be a date if you order Raisin Bran.
It's not a date. So how's your thing going -- your dancing thing?
It's good. How's your restraining order?
I wouldn't actually call the restraining order "my thing, ?
but getting back with Nikki is, and I've been doing pretty well.
Except for a minor incident at the doctor's office.
And the so-called incident with the weights.
万圣节快乐
Yeah. That was a thing with my parents. I wish I could just
你好
explain it all in a letter to Nikki because it was minor and I could
just explain it and let her know that I'm actually not out of
control and that I'm actually doing really well.
I can get a letter to Nikki. I see her sometimes with my sister.
请坐
谢谢
我要一碗提子麦麸
很好！
茶
It would be so amazing if you could get a letter to Nikki from me.
I'd have to hide it from Veronica. She's not into breaking the law,
你看起来很漂亮
which this letter would definitely be doing.
谢谢
But you would do it?
提子麦麸  牛奶
I'd have to be careful. I'm already on thin ice with my family,
谢谢
you should hear how I lost my job.
How did you lose your job?
By... having sex with everybody in the office.
Everybody?
I was very depressed after Tommy died. It was a lot of people.
想分一点吗？
We don't have to talk about it.
你为什么点提子麦麸？
Thanks.
你为什么点茶？
How many were there?
Eleven.
Wow.
因为你点了提子麦麸
I know.
I'm not gonna talk about it anymore.
我点这个是不想让你误会
Okay.
以为这是个约会
Can I ask you one more question?
就算你点提子麦麸  这还是有可能是个约会
Were there any women?
这不是约会
Yes.
Really?
工作如何  跳舞什么的
Yes.
What was that like?
挺好  你的限制令进行的怎么样了？
Hot.
限制令可不是我的工作
Jesus Christ. Was it like... older women,
不过跟尼基重归于好这件事  进展还不错
a sexy teacher who wants to seduce you-
虽然在医生看来有点小摩擦
Made me sit on her lap and do things? Yeah.
就是你声称被杠铃砸了的那次
是啊  是跟我父母之间的问题
What? You sat on her lap?
我想写封信给尼基解释一下
Mm-hmm.
因为这事没什么大不了
She told you what to do?
Mm-hmm.
我可以解释一下  告诉她我并没有失控
Oh... my God. Nikki hated when I talked like this.
Made me feel like such a pervert. Maybe we should change the subject.
我恢复得很好
I don't mind it.
You don't, do you.
No. But then people were getting into fights in the parking lot at
work, and in the bathroom... and the boss called me in to his office and
我可以帮你捎信给尼基
我偶尔会跟我姐一起去见她
tried to pin it all on me. So I accused him of harassment and then
they fired me, sent me home and put me on some meds.
要是你能帮我捎信给尼基  实在感激不尽
I get it. The song that was playing when my wife...
我得瞒着维罗妮卡  这封信可是犯法的
她可不愿意沾上
was in the shower with the history teacher...
I heard about that.
你不怕吧？
... it was my wedding song and when I hear it, I go kinda crazy.
Sometimes I hear it when it's not even playing.
我也得小心  我跟家里已经闹得够僵了
Wow.
Yeah. So they put me on medication, which I feel ashamed of.
你也应该听说我是怎么丢了工作的
你是怎么丢了工作的？
Yeah.
把所有同事睡了个遍
So I know.
You do.
I just gotta get a strategy, you know?
Me too.
所有？
We'd better get back to the letter.
汤米死后  我很低落  我们办公室人不少
Yeah, let's get back to the letter.
What if you told Nikki when Veronica was in the bathroom?
我们还是别聊这个吧
谢谢
Yes. Yes, that could work. I love that.
到底有多少个？
11个
了解
Oh, my God, I'm gonna go home and write the letter right now.
我不会再提这事了
好
Can I at least finish my tea?
我能再问个问题吗？
Wait, what?
My tea. Can I finish it?
Wait a minute. Did Veronica tell Nikki about our dinner?
其中有女人吗？
Why would she do that? Was it a test?
有
真的？
真的
I kinda got that feeling, yeah.
感觉怎么样？
Goddamn it. I knew it. It was a test. How did I do?
爽
天啊
I think I did pretty well.
是不是那种…年纪大一点的
Yeah, she said you were cool, basically.
Basically? Was I some percentage not cool?
性感女教师引诱你…
No, she said you were cool, but you know.
让我坐在她腿上搞？是的
No, I don't know.
什么  坐在她腿上？
Sort of how you are. It's fine, relax.
她告诉你该怎么做？
What do you mean? How am I? What does that mean?
天哪  尼基讨厌我这样讲话
Sort of like me.
"Sort of like you"? I hope to God she didn't tell Nikki that.
让我听起来像个变态  我们换个话题吧
我无所谓的
Why?
你无所谓吧
Because, it's just not right, lumping you and I together,
无所谓  但后来他们就在上班时
I mean, it's just wrong. And Nikki wouldn't like that.
在停车场和盥洗室打了起来
老板把我叫到办公室
Especially after all the shit you just told me.
把这些都怪到我头上  我就指控他性骚扰
You think that I'm crazier than you.
Because, well, we're different, I mean-
他们就把我炒了  赶我回家  逼我吃药
Oh, my God. Ugh. You're killing me.
我懂的
我老婆跟那个教历史的一起洗澡时
正在放一首歌
You know what? Forget I offered to help you.
我听说了
那是我婚礼上放的歌  我现在一听到就会抓狂
有时候  明明没在放  我脑子里还是会听到
Forget the entire fucking idea. Cause that must have been
fucking crazy because I am so much crazier than you.
他们就把我关进医院  这很丢人
Keep your voice down.
所以我能理解
I'm just the crazy slut with a dead husband!
是的
Forget it!
我得想个对策
Shut the fuck up.
我也是
Fuck you!
You shut the fuck up!
我们还是说回那封信吧
Tiffany! Hey! Tiffany!
好  说回那封信
你趁着维罗妮卡上厕所时告诉尼基怎么样？
对  这主意不错
Slow down, Raisin Bran.
天哪  我得赶紧回家写信
Hey, come on. Look, I don't think you're crazy, all right?
起码得等我把茶喝完吧？
什么？
Yes, you do.
茶  能让我喝完吗？
No, I don't.
慢着
You told your therapist that you were in a superior mental illness
维罗妮卡有没有把我们吃晚餐的事告诉尼基？
category, didn't you?
她为什么要那么做  那是个测试吗？
What? Hey, calm down! Hey-
Just leave me alone!
Can I just explain myself, please?
我也这么觉得
I didn't want Nikki to think that I was associated with that kind of
该死  我就知道那是个测试  我做得怎么样？
sexual behavior because I've never done anything like that, okay?
You may not have experienced the shit that I did.
我觉得还不错
她说你算是很冷静
But you loved hearing about it, didn't you?
算是？ 那就是还有几分不冷静了？
You are afraid to be alive, you're afraid to live. You're a hypocrite.
不  她说你很冷静  不过  你懂的
You're a conformist. You're a liar. I opened up to you and you judged me.
不懂
就是你的本性嘛  没事的  别担心
You are an asshole. You are an asshole!
Get off of me!  Get off!
什么叫我的本性  什么意思？
You're harassing me!
就跟我差不多
Hey, hey!
跟你差不多？ 但愿她没跟尼基这么说
He's harassing me!
Get off!
Take it easy. Dude, relax.
He's harassing me!!
为什么？
Bro, get off of me.
因为  把你跟我混为一谈  这不太对
He's harassing me!!
Hey, hey, stop, stop. Stop, all right?
Hey, get off of me! Shut up, shut up.
这就是不对  尼基听了会不高兴的
Stop it.
尤其是你刚才跟我说了那些破事之后
你觉得我比你更疯
因为  那个  我们是不一样的
Hey, hey, hey, get off me!
What are you doing? Come on. What are you doing?
天哪  你好狠啊
What are you doing to these kids?
Are you being a punk on Halloween with these kids?
You wanna go back to Baltimore? Is that what you wanna do?
I didn't, I didn't, I didn't-
知道吗  别指望我帮你了
It's the kids!
Honestly He didn't do anything, it was all the kids.
忘掉这个该死的主意吧  实在太荒唐了
Let's go, clear out, nothing going on here.
因为我比你疯得多
Come on man what you gonna do about that song? You gonna go your whole life scared of that song?
小声点
我就是个死了丈夫的骚货！
It's just a song. Don't make it a monster.
去死吧!
Come on breath! There's no song playing. There's no song.
你闭嘴！
去你妈的！
你才闭嘴！
蒂芙尼！
That's it.
That's it. There you go. I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
慢着  提子麦麸
等等  我没觉得你疯
I'm sorry.
你就是觉得
I took it too far.
我没有
I'm sorry.
你跟你的心理医生说
Hey, is he messing with you?
你的精神病比较高级  对不对？
No, no. No, this was just a joke. This is a joke I started.
什么  冷静点
There's a restraining order on this guy.
离我远点！
I know, I have a stupid sense of humor.
能听我解释一下吗？
That's not a good thing to do.
我不想让尼基觉得我会跟那种…
Well, I'm fucked up. What can I tell you? I'm sorry.
You're Tommy's widow, right?
不正当的性行为扯上关系
Yes, I'm Tommy's crazy whore widow, minus the whore thing for the most part.
因为我从来就没做过那种事
你是没做过
You're a funny girl. You wanna get a drink sometime?
但倒是挺爱听的  不是吗？
你没胆子活出自我  没胆子做自己
What'd I say? She doesn't, she doesn't do that anymore.
你是个伪君子
只敢随大流  你是个骗子
我对你敞开心扉  你却瞧不起我
你这个混球  你这个混球！
放开我！
你在骚扰我！
I'm sorry about what I said in the diner.
他在骚扰我！
I know. I know you didn't mean it.
滚开！
放松点  老兄  别惹事
I didn't mean it at all.
他在骚扰我！！
I know, you say shit you don't mean all the time.
兄弟  放开我
All the time. I'll still give your letter to Nikki, don't worry.
他在骚扰我！！
别这样  别这样  好吗？
Wow. I really appreciate that, Tiffany.
放开我  闭嘴
I know you do.
别这样
You do? Yeah, sure. I'll see you tomorrow? With the letter?
I'll bet I know what happened if only one is missing.
放开我！
你在干什么  你在干什么？
Either Dolores or Pat needed an envelope and one of em took it.
你跟这些小孩闹什么？
跟他们一起扮万圣节流氓吗？
That's the only answer. No, no, no.
你想回巴尔的摩吗  你想吗？
Dolores, somebody was in my study. Who took one of my envelopes?
不想  不想
Somebody took an envelope.
Maybe we should call the FBI.
是那些小孩的错！
Don't make fun. This is serious.
他真的什么都没做  都是那些小孩搞的鬼
What FBI? Come on, let's take a look. I'll show you what this is.
I'm gonna just explain to you something. I mean, you know what
走吧  走吧  没什么好看的
I'm doing, honey. This everything, like this.
你打算拿那首歌怎么办？
I got this, it all corresponds.
难不成要怕它一辈子吗？
Dad, I borrowed one of your envelopes.
I hope that's not a problem
不过是首歌  别把它想象成梦魇
No, it's not okay. It's not okay. You gotta ask.
Do not go in my study or I will eat you!?
深呼吸  那首歌没在放  没在放
It's not funny, it's not funny.
What's everybody making a joke out of this for?
Dolores, you are so beautiful!
那首歌没在放
Stop that! Hey, hey, hey, stop, stop, stop!
Listen, a lot of envelopes go in and out of my office every day
after games with a lot of cash in
就这样
em. So show some respect for what I do.
就这样  很好  对不起
Yeah, I know. I saw two-seven-four.
I just wanted to tell you the number.
Thank you.
But the envelope was empty. I'm sorry, you were sleeping.
I didn't want to wake you, but I needed an envelope.
You didn't want to wake me? He didn't want to wake me.
对不起
He doesn't have a problem complaining about Ernest fucking Hemingway.
是我反应过度了
对不起
He doesn't have a problem asking for his wedding video-
他骚扰你了吗？
没有  我开玩笑的
Be nice. It's game day! I'm makin crabby snacks and homemades.
这家伙有人身限制令呢
Yeah, come on, Dad, be nice. Come on, she's making crabby snacks and
我知道  我玩笑开的过头了
homemades. Come on, Dad!
这种玩笑可开不得
我玩砸了呗  你还要我怎样  对不起
What are you so up about?
你是汤米的遗孀吧？
He's very happy. I'm happy.
没错  我就是汤米的疯骚遗孀
No, you're so up, up, up, up.
不过“骚”字能免则免吧
Isn't that a good thing?
这妹子有意思  有空喝一杯吗？
You're just up, up, up. I don't know what that is.
Are you taking the proper dosage of your medication?
Am I taking the right dose? Of course I am.
- 我说错什么了？ - 她不会再做那种事了
Okay. Taking a little bit too many or something?
No, if I was taking that, I'd be on the floor, Dad.
Just stay with us. Stay for the game. Spend some family time.
Dad, I can't. Look, I'm ready to go.
Spend family time. Wait, you mean OCD, superstitious time?
Come on, your dad needs a winner. Help him out.
Come on. I can't. It's the Seahawks.
对不起  我不该说那种话
Put on the jersey and stay, please. Please. It's important, please.
我知道  我知道你不是那意思
我真的不是那意思
我知道  你讲的鬼话从来都言不由衷
What are you up to, Pat? Nothing, come on.
- 都不是 - 放心  尼基的信我会帮你捎的
What's in the envelope?
太谢谢你了  蒂芙尼
Yeah, what are you doing? What's in that envelope?
Guys, I'm beating the song! I'm on the scoreboard!
我知道
I'm playing down field! I feel great!
- 是吗 - 是啊
那明天见吧  我把信给你
只要少了一个  我就肯定知道
可能多洛蕾丝或者帕特拿了一个信封
Hey, how you doin'? Is Tiffany here?
What do you want with her?
- 肯定是这样 - 不会的
Is that another creep? What do you want, creep? Just beat it.
Whoa, no, no, no. No, I'm married.
有人进我书房了吗？ 我少了个信封
Oh, great, a married creep. I'm her friend.
有人拿了个信封
We go running. Have you guys not seen us? I took her to the diner.
问问联邦调查局吧
She's not here.
别开玩笑  我说真的
Hi, guys. How's it going? Hey. Is Tiffany home? Go away.
I know her. I know her, we've dated. We still date.
什么联邦调查局？ 来看个究竟吧
听我给你解释一下 你知道我在干什么
What are you doing here? I've called her, I've texted her.
亲爱的  东西都在这儿
I still haven't heard back. We used to work together-
Just get the hell out of here...
都是信
I just wanted to give you my card to give to her.
爸  我借你的信封用用
Another rude creep. Listen to what he's saying.
你不介意吧
Listen to what he's saying. What's he saying?
不行  你起码得先问问我
He's saying you're being rude.
“入我书房者  杀无赦！”
How am I being rude?
Oh, you know. You know. Come on.
开什么玩笑
Sometimes it's okay with girls like this, they wanna have fun and sometimes -
这有什么好笑的？
-it's not because they got a broken wing, and they're hurt,
多洛蕾丝  你真是我的女神！
and they're an easy target. And in this case, in this particular case,
别闹  我说了  别闹！
I think that wing is being fixed.
赛后每天都有很多信封进出我办公室
And you gotta make sure it gets mended. And you're gettin' in the
way of that right now, okay? Because she's sensitive and she's
里面装着现金
smart, she's artistic. This is a great girl and you gotta be
请尊重我的事情
respectful of that. Come on.
我知道  我看见上面写着274
Let me walk you down to your car. You're a better guy than this.
我只是来把数目告诉你
谢谢
但信封是空的  很抱歉  你在睡觉
I can see it in your eyes. She just texted me!
我不想吵醒你  可我需要一个信封
你还不想吵醒我？ 他还不想吵醒我
他不想跟我唠叨什么海明威
他不想找我要什么婚礼录像
别计较了  今天是比赛日  我去给你们做点心
Hey! Hey, wait a second! What are you doing? What happened?
爸  别计较了  有点心呢
How come you weren't outside? What the hell's going on?
来吧  爸！
I can't, I can't do it.
你怎么这么兴奋？
What do you mean, you can't do it? You can't do what?
- 他很开心啊 - 我很开心
I can't give the letter to Nikki.
Tiffany, what are you talking about? What do you mean you can't
不  你看起来过于兴奋了
这不好吗？
give the letter to Nikki? Because what am I getting in return?
你兴奋成那样  我却不知道你在乐什么
What are you doing for me? You said! You said if I wrote a letter,
你用药没缺斤少两吧？
you'd get it to Nikki. I know. That was the set-up.
我的用药量？ 当然没错
Because I do this time after time after time, I do all this shit for
那你是药吃多了还是怎样？
other people and then I wake up and, and I'm empty, I have nothing!
要是我吃多了  早就趴下了
待在家里看看比赛  享受一下天伦之乐
What are you talking about? You seem like you're a tough girl to
爸  不行  我要走了
me. Why don't you just do things on your own?
天伦之乐？ 你是指你的强迫症和运气论？
I always get myself in these fucking situations. I give
everything to other people and nobody ever, I never -- I don't get
拜托  你爸需要一个胜场  帮帮他吧
- 不行 - 对手是海鹰队
what I want, okay? I'm not my sister.
把球衣穿上  留下来  拜托了
这场球很重要  拜托了
- 你要去干嘛  帕特？ - 没什么
Alright, well, ask for you. What can I do for you?
信封里装着什么？
你要干什么？ 信封里是什么东西？
I can't do it. Tiffany, what do you want me to do?
我要打败那首歌  我已经领先了！
我要赢到底  加油！
Think of something. There's this thing.
There's a thing, okay. What kind of thing?
It's a thing, it's a thing. It's a, it's a dance thing.
It's a dance thing, all right.
It's a competition thing at the Benjamin Franklin Hotel.
Tommy would never do it with me and I missed it every single year.
Well, Tommy's dead, so he's not gonna fucking do it.
你好吗？ 蒂芙尼在吗？
Would you please! I don't have a filter when I talk.
Can we have one conversation without you reminding me that my
你找她干什么？
又是个变态  你想干嘛  滚开
goddamn husband is dead?
不是那么回事  我结婚了
Yes, I'm sorry. I'm sorry. Okay, I'm sorry.
- 好  已婚变态 - 我是她朋友
But I can only do it if I have a partner... and now I'm about to miss
我们一起跑步  你们没见过吗？
it for another year.
她不在
Whoa, whoa, whoa, I'm not gonna fuckin' dance with you.
- 你们好  蒂芙尼在吗？ - 滚开
What are you talking about?
What, your schedule is so busy? Grapes of Wrath?and watching
我认识她的  真的  我们交往过
football with your dad?
现在还在交往
Tiffany, I'm not gonna do a dance with you.
- 你来这干嘛？ - 我给她打过电话  发过短信
All right, then I'm not giving her your fucking letter.
她一直没回  我们以前是同事
Wait a second! But you promised you would do this.
给我赶紧滚
Think about it.
请把我的名片转交给她
- 又是个无礼的变态 - 听听他在说什么
Well, I already did do something for you, you know.
听听他在说什么  他怎么说的？
他说你很无礼
我怎么无礼了？
I took care of that jerkoff that was in front of your house.
你自己知道
有的姑娘只想玩玩  你跟她们玩玩没问题
What? Jordie?
有的姑娘不行  她们受了伤  感情很脆弱
Let me ask you something. Do you call him when you're lonely?
That encourages him, Tiffany. You shouldn't do it.
不能趁虚而入  至于这个姑娘
Couldn't you say the same about you and Nikki?
我想她的伤口正在自愈
It's not at all like me and Nikki.
你应该帮她完全复原  你现在有机会
What are you talking about? We're in love and we're married.
It's completely different.
她很敏感  很聪明
How are you in love? Tell me about that. The big Nikki love.
又有艺术天分  她是个好姑娘
你应该要尊重她  走吧
Tell me about it, I wanna understand it.
我送你回你的车里去  你不是那种混蛋
We have a very unconventional chemistry, it makes people feel
- 我看得出来 - 她刚刚发了短信给我！
awkward, but not me. She's the most beautiful woman I've ever been with.
Wow. It's electric between us,
Okay? Yeah, we wanna change each other, but that's normal, couples wanna do that,
I want her to stop dressing like she dresses, I want her to
等等！你在干嘛？
stop acting so superior to me, okay? And she wanted me to lose
怎么回事？
你为什么不出来  到底怎么回事？
weight and stop my mood swings, both of which I've done.
不行  我办不到
什么意思  你办不到什么？
I mean, people fight. Couples fight. We would fight, we wouldn't talk for a
我不能捎信给尼基
couple weeks. That's normal. She always wanted the best for me.
蒂芙尼  为什么不能捎信给尼基？
She wanted me to be passionate and compassionate. And that's a good
我这么做有什么好处呢？
thing. You know? I just, look, I'm my best self today, and I think
- 你为我做过什么？ - 你说只要我写信
she's her best self today, and our love's gonna be fucking amazing.
- 你就捎给尼基  说好了的 - 我知道
因为我总干蠢事  我总为别人做这做那
It's gonna be amazing, and you're gonna be amazing, and she's gonna
be amazing, and you're not gonna be that guy that's gonna take
到头来发现自己什么都没有
advantage of a situation without offering to do something back.
你瞎说什么呢  你明明看起来很强势
So think about the dance thing.
怎么会不为自己考虑呢？
我老是把自己搞得那么狼狈
替别人两肋插刀  却从来没有人…
Danny, you're out of the hospital? And you're here on game day?
我没法事事如愿  好吗？ 我不像我姐姐
I'm out. It's official, man. They didn't convert me to my
Mental Hygiene Law admission status within two thirds of the maximum length
好吧  那我问你  我又能为你做什么？
of my felony sentence, so I'm out. They had to let me go.
- 我办不到 - 蒂芙尼  你想让我做什么？
I never understand what he's saying.
Okay, jailhouse lawyer, come on, let's come back and sit down the
way you were before.
- 想想吧 - 有件事
What a treat! Whoa, whoa, whoa. Dad's got you sitting here?
有件事  什么事？
Oh, yeah. He calls me Jailhouse Lawyer. ?
是件…是件跳舞的事
Hold the remote the way you were holding it before.
Okay. And now you're holding the remote?
跳舞的事  好
And it's working. Your dad's a genius.
是富兰克林酒店的比赛
Now sit up. And Danny's the good luck charm?
汤米以前从不陪我去  我年年都去不了
Danny's from you. This is your house, so it comes down to you.
汤米死了更去不了了
- 你有必要吗！ - 我讲话老是没遮没拦
You're the one. Yeah, you're the one, Pat.
你能不能别总提
Superstition, Danny. I don't know.
我死了丈夫这破事？
Come sit down.
好吧  对不起
Don't disappear doing God knows what with that Tiffany Maxwell.
但我得有舞伴才能参加比赛
Dad, Dad, Dad. She's my friend. Why would you say that?
不然今年又得错过了
Oh, she's a mess. You gotta be careful. She goes to a lot of therapy.
我才不会跟你去跳舞
I go to a lot of therapy, Ronnie. What are you trying to say?
你瞎说什么呢？
你有什么要忙的？ 看《愤怒的葡萄》
I'm just saying- Am I messed up?
还是陪你爸看球？
Why don't you stop judging people? You judge everybody. You're the one
蒂芙尼  我不会跟你去跳什么舞的
who has a messed up marriage.
那好  我也不会帮你捎什么信的
I'm just looking out for you, I'm just looking out for you. She's unstable.
等等  你答应了的
What's wrong with your marriage? What's wrong with your marriage?
想想看吧
Nothing's wrong!
You should have seen when I was at his house. It's like a circus over there.
我已经帮你做了件事了
Shh, shh. What are you talking about? I'm not gonna hide this.
你为我做了什么
You need to deal with it. Stop breaking my balls.
我帮你赶走了你家门口那个变态
Oh!!!! I got you an iPod. Whoa! Is this for me?
谁？你说乔迪？
你是不是一空虚了就打电话找他？
Yeah. Well, that's my old iPod, but-
Oh, buddy, thank you. That's so nice of you. Wow.
那只会让他得寸进尺  你不该这么做
Thirty-two gigabytes. How many songs is that? Seven thousand.
你跟尼基不也这样吗？
我跟尼基根本就不是这样
Oh, yeah, you got The Stranglers. You love The Stranglers.
你胡说什么  我们相爱  我们是夫妻
Oh, the Sex Pistols. The Clash. Got some Clash.
这完全不一样
你们怎么相爱的  给我讲讲吧
Oh, West Side Story. ?Yeah, West Side Story. ?It makes me peaceful.
你跟尼基的爱情故事
给我讲讲  我不明白
Maria, I just met a girl named Maria... ? Right, right, right.
我们之间十分不寻常  这让别人觉得不舒服
And then when I'm angry, which is a lot these days, I go to the
garage... Metallica... Megadeth. I start fucking smashing shit.
但我不会  她是我交往过的最美的姑娘
我们之间是有火花的
没错  我们也想改变对方
但这很正常  每对情侣都这样
You gotta get your marriage together.
我想改变她的穿衣风格
I start breaking shit, and I hurt my hand. And -
我想让她别再对我指手画脚  她想让我减肥
Ronnie, that's fucked up. Yeah, but it makes me feel better.
别再乱发脾气  我也正在为之努力
It's like my therapy, you know?
不和是人之常情  每对情侣都有不和
When I'm with Nikki, I'm never gonna do stuff like that...
我们也会  我们会几个礼拜不说话
这很正常  她总想让我做得更好
Whoa, Nikki? What's all this about Nikki?
她想让我变得更有热情  更有同情心
Pan from the framed photo of Jake on foyer wall, to Jake on the stairs above.
这是好事  你明白吗？
A restraining order is nothing to fool with, bro. Holy shit, look at you! You
我为她变成了一个更好的人
我想她也是  我们的爱情会妙不可言
are fit! You look absolutely amazing. You feel good?
妙不可言  你会妙不可言  她会妙不可言
How you doing, Jake? Good. You look like Schwarzenegger in his prime.
你别想什么都不做就让我捎信
Didn't I say you wouldn't recognize him?
So, listen, I'm sorry that I didn't come see you down at the hospital.
还是考虑一下跳舞的事吧
You know how those places creep me out, and the firm's been expanding.
I've been helping Pop with the restaurant cause he needs to have
丹尼  你出院了？ 你来看比赛的吗？
a legitimate business. He needs a tax return. With all the money that
我出院了  正式的
he's making with his bookmaking, they're gonna come after him. And
then it looks like I'm making, I'm gonna make partner at the firm.
他们没在我三分之二的刑期上限内
Well, I don't even know what to say to you anymore. You lost your wife,
把我转入精神卫生法许可状态
就放我出来了  他们别无选择
I'm getting engaged, and I wanna be able to tell you about those kind
我从来听不懂他说什么
狱房律师  来  回来坐下
of things. You lost your house, I'm getting a new house. You lost your
像以前一样
太棒了  爸爸让你坐这儿的？
job, things are going great for me at the firm.
- 是啊 - 他管我叫“狱房律师”
Maybe stop talking about all the stuff that's good for you and bad
拿着遥控板  跟以前一样
for him. Just, you know, leave it alone. We're watching the game.
好  现在遥控板归你来拿了？
这很管用的  你爸爸是个天才
You know what, I'm just gonna, I'm just gonna, I'm just gonna stop
- 坐这 - 丹尼也是福星？
talking. I'm gonna shut my mouth.
从你身上沾来的  这是你家  在你身上
- 你才是福星 - 没错  你才是福星  帕特
As my friend Danny would say I got nothing but love for you, brother.
少迷信了  丹尼
过来坐下
别又溜去跟那个蒂芙尼・麦克斯维尔鬼混
爸  她是我朋友  你是什么意思？
她是个大麻烦  小心点  她常去看心理医生
我也常去  罗尼  你这话是什么意思？
That's right. That's right. That's nice. That's nice.
- 我只是想说… - 我也是个大麻烦吗？
你凭什么指责别人？谁都看不顺眼
Well, thank God, finally. DeSean Jackson. Yeah. Did it fit?
你自己的婚姻不还是一团糟
我只是给你提个醒
你婚姻怎么了？
I wore it to Ronnie's for dinner.
没怎么了！
你要是跟我一起去他家看看就知道了
Beautiful jersey. I love that jersey.
简直就像个马戏团
Veronica didn't like it. Veronica hates the jersey.
你说什么呢？ 不要藏着掖着
Whatever you do, watch out for that restraining order, okay?
- 你总要面对的 - 别给我找麻烦了
- 我给你带了个iPod - 是给我的吗？
Don't let Tiffany get you in trouble.
是的  这是我以前用过的  不过…
Pat, you're up to something, I know.
老兄  谢谢你  你太够意思了
People like Tiffany, or Danny, or me, maybe we know something that
- 32G容量 - 能装多少歌？
7000首
you guys don't know, okay? Did you ever think about that? Maybe we
“行刑者”  你喜欢“行刑者”
understand something because we're more-
- “性手枪”  “冲击” - 有几首“冲击”的
We have a sixth sense. I mean, everybody's got it. Everybody's
just not in touch with it.
Oh, no. How you doing, Pat? Jesus.
- 《西区故事》 - 没错  《西区故事》
I guess his sixth sense forgot to tell him the cops were coming.
能舒缓心情
- 我认识了个姑娘  她叫玛利亚… - 没错
I'm taking him back to the hospital.
最近每当我怒火中烧的时候
What? No, no, he passed his thing, right?
First of all, check with the latest legal development.
我就躲进车库听重金属砸东西
Well, we got a call that they did convert you to a Mental Hygiene Law
admission status by the deadline of your sentence, so... .
Wait a minute. Are you an Eagles fan or are you not an Eagles fan?
I'm an Eagles fan.
你得把婚姻料理好
Well then, what's the problem? He's not goin' anywhere. Just let him
我开始砸东西  把手都砸伤了
finish the game, that's all. The handkerchief is working. We're
- 罗尼  这糟透了 - 可这能让我好过点
killing the Seahawks, twenty-seventen.
What's the matter with you? Let him stay, please!
这就是我的心理治疗  懂吗？
我跟尼基在一起的时候  从来不会做这些…
I don't know what the hell you're talking about the handkerchief?
尼基？ 怎么扯到尼基了？
And I'm glad that the Seahawks are losing and we're winning, but I
gotta take Danny McDaniels back to Baltimore, alright? He can contest
老弟  限制令可不是闹着玩的
his case from Baltimore.
天哪  瞧瞧你啊！
Not correct about the Mental Hygiene Law. You're not correct.
你瘦了  看起来好极了  感觉怎么样？
Come on. You guys oughta be ashamed of yourselves.
你好吗  杰克？
很好  你看上去像施瓦辛格
我不是说了吗  我差点没认出他来
很抱歉我没去医院看你
我一去那种地方就不自在  公司又在扩张
我在帮爸爸开餐馆  因为他得做个合法生意
他需要纳税申报单
赌球挣了那么多钱
I used the insurance money to build this. I designed it. All the floors
他们肯定会找上门来
那样的话  表面上那些钱就是我赚的
are hard oak. It has good bounce for dancers. Wow.
我们算是合作伙伴
I'm not that great of a dancer, but who cares? It's therapy and it's
我不知道还能说些什么  你老婆丢了
fun. And the walls are good cause I can play music really loud
而我要订婚了 我还有很多这类事情可以告诉你
without anybody hearing. Where do you sleep?
Upstairs. It's a garage, I just renovated it. You know, I was
你丢了房子  而我要买新房子了
thinking about putting a ballet barre here.
你丢了工作  我的公司却蒸蒸日上
When are you gonna give it to her?
What?
别再讲什么你过得有多好  他过得多不好
The letter to Nikki.
别管这些了  我们在看球呢
Probably tonight. Really?
知道吗  我不多嘴了
Ronnie and Veronica and I are gonna see her tonight.
我还是闭嘴吧
Oh, I actually changed the first paragraph. I did this thing about
Shakespeare and how it's very romantic-
Mm-hmm. -and that maybe in the future if
就像我朋友丹尼会说的那样
she wanted to go dancing, I can be able to do that because of all the
training that-No, that's good, that's really good.
I assume you're a good teacher.
Yeah. I mean, I hope so.
Maybe you can teach us both, you know what I mean?
我对你只有崇敬之情  哥哥
And I also mentioned how generous it is, what I'm doing for you.
Yeah. Mm-hmm. It's really generous.
You know, being of service.
Yeah. To your need. Uh-huh.
很好  很好
All right, let's start simple. Start at that corner, walk towards me.
Walk across the room.
谢天谢地  终于没事了
- 德肖恩・杰克逊 - 合身吗？
Can we do something else besides the dance deal?
Are you fucking kidding me?
我还穿着它去罗尼家做客了呢
I'm good with a hammer. You want me to fix something? A deal is a deal.
I know. Okay. I was just suggesting that maybe there's a better scenario.
很漂亮  我喜欢那件球衣
- 维罗妮卡不喜欢 - 维罗妮卡可讨厌那件球衣了
Why don't you walk towards me like I'm Nikki.
不管怎样  注意那个限制令  好吗？
别被蒂芙尼卷进去了
And the only way to convey how much you've missed me is by your walk. By your slow walk.
帕特  你有事瞒着我们  我看得出来
像蒂芙尼  丹尼或是我这样的人没准懂一些
You can't talk. Only walk.
你们不懂的事情  想过没有？
I'm not doing it. Do it. No. That's stupid.
我们懂一些事情  因为我们更…
我们有第六感  每个人都有
No walk, no letter. Walk to me like I'm Nikki, come on. Do it. I'm Nikki. Come on.
不过并不是每个人都会用
- 天啊  不 - 你好吗  帕特？
他的第六感大概忘了告诉他  警察来了
You're not Nikki.
我要把他带回医院
Don't look up until you're halfway here.
不行  他不是通过那玩意了吗？
先去查查最新法案吧
我们接到电话
他们没在你三分之二的刑期上限内
把你转入精神卫生法许可状态  所以…
慢着  你是老鹰队的球迷吗？
我是老鹰队球迷
Yes. Do you feel that? That's emotion.
那还有什么关系？ 他哪儿也不会去
I don't feel anything.
就让他看完比赛吧  福星很管用呢
我们要打败海鹰队了  20比17
Has anybody ever told you how Tommy died?
你是怎么啦  就让他留下吧！
我听不懂你说的“福星”是怎么回事
海鹰要输了  我们要赢了  我很高兴
We were married for three years and
可我得带丹尼回巴尔的摩
five days, and I loved him. But for the last couple months, I just
wasn't into sex at all. It just felt like we were so different and
他要为自己的案子辩护
这不符合精神卫生法  你们错了
I was depressed. Some of that is just me, some of it was he wanted
你们这些人真该替自己害臊
me to have kids and I have a hard enough time taking care of myself.
I don't think that makes me a criminal. Anyway one night after
dinner, he drove to Victoria's Secret at King of Prussia Mall and
got some lingerie to get something going. And on the way back, he
我用保险金建的这里  我自己设计的
stopped on 76 to help a guy with a flat tire and he got hit by a car
地板都是硬橡木的  适合舞者弹跳
and killed. And the Victoria's Secret box was still in the front
我跳得没那么好  可有关系吗？
这有治疗功效  而且很有意思
seat. That's a feeling.
墙也很好  我把音乐声开得再大
- 外面也听不见 - 你在哪睡觉？
楼上  这是个车库  我只是改建了一下
我想在这搭个芭蕾扶手
你什么时候给她？
什么？
给尼基的信
- 今晚吧 - 真的？
我跟罗尼和维罗妮卡今晚要去看她
我修改了第一段  引用了莎士比亚
还承诺…
- 嗯 - 将来要是她想跳舞的话
我可以陪她跳
- 因为我已经学过了 - 不错  真不错
我假定你教得很好了
我是说  我希望如此
也许你可以同时教我们两个
我还提到了  我为你做的这件事有多慷慨
嗯  确实很慷慨
任你差遣
- 是 - 听你所需
从简单的开始  从那个角落朝我走过来
穿过整个房间
除了跳舞  我能干点别的什么吗？
开什么玩笑？
我很会使锤子  你有什么要修的吗？
我们说好的
我知道  我只是不想闹笑话而已
你何不把我当成尼基  朝我走过来
唯一能表达你对我的思念的
就是你的步态  你缓慢的步态
你不能说话  只能用步态表达
我不干  蠢死了
你不走  我就不捎信
朝我走过来  当我是尼基
来吧  我就是尼基
你不是尼基
走到一半再抬头
对了  感觉到没有
我什么感觉也没有
你知道汤米是怎么死的吗？
没有
我们结婚三年零五天
我很爱他  但最后那几个月
我毫无性致  感觉我们像是两个世界的人
我很沮丧  部分原因是我的性格
另一部分原因是他想要孩子
可我连自己都照顾不好
我觉得这不是我的错
不管怎样  一天晚饭后
他开车去维多利亚的秘密
给我买了几件内衣来帮帮忙
回家路上有个人轮胎没气了
他就停下来帮他  结果被车撞死了
装着内衣的盒子还放在前座上
Whoa! Slow down. What?
这就叫感觉
Your father wanted you to have this.
He wants me to have- all this Eagles information.
It's his living. Um, tell Dad thanks.
Your father expects to spend time with you, Pat.
Football stays out of this place, so does Lord of the Flies. ?
Wait, wait, no, no, no, what are you doing? I'm behind on my syllabus.
I don't give a fuck. What the hell are you doing? Hey, hey!
Did you just throw that outside?
What? You're not gonna read that shit on my time. I can tell you all
about the Lord of the Flies. ?It's a bunch of boys on an island and
they have a conch -- they have a shell -- and whoever has the conch
has the power and they can talk. And if you don't have the conch,
then you don't have the power. And then there's a little chubby boy,
and they call him Piggy and they're really mean, and then there's a
murder. I mean, humanity is just nasty and there's no silver lining.
Wow. That was a great synopsis. I still need to read it, though.
Who's that? What the... . ? What are you doing here, man?
If one of your two supervising physicians loses their license,
then your whole ajudication is thrown out.
How'd you know we were here?
I went by your parents' house looking for you and they told me
you was over here.
Danny, this is Tiffany. Tiffany, this is Danny.
Hello. Pat told me about you. So is the girl, that you wrote about?
Yeah. What? He wrote about me? I'm the girl?
He wrote about you, all right. What'd he say?
He said you guys was helping each other out and you were nice and had
a mouth on you, that you were mouthy, but-
Whoa, whoa, that's enough.
No, please, tell me more about what he said in the letter.
Yeah, anything you wanna know, I'll just tell you. It was nothing.
It was just a very general letter.
Cool. She's fine. She is my friend with an F. ?
A capital F. ? For friend. ?
Hey, can I see what you guys are doing?
Yeah. Okay. That's it?
Why? What is it, what is it, what is it.
Can I say something? Do you mind? No.
You sure? Just say it. Say it.
No, please. I think Pat, you should be facing Tiffany.
Let me show you, Pat, let me show you what I mean. You gotta come at
her with a little bit more soul, man.
You should move more hips.
Just, just sort of come in, Pat, come in like this. And... .
Okay. Yeah. Can you move em a little bit more? Yeah, that's it.
Move em a bit more.
You could turn around, too, there's nothing wrong with that.
Yeah. You're pretty good. Mm, yeah.
Okay, we got it, we got it. Okay. Okay.
Come on, Pat, come on. A little bit more soul. Black it up, Pat.
Black it up? You know damn well what it means.
I got an idea. Come get some, Pat. Come get some.
- 喂！等等 - 怎么？
你爸让你带着这个
Shuffle back, shuffle back. Shuffle back, shuffle back.
他要我看…全是老鹰队的新闻
- 这是他的事业 - 帮我谢谢爸
Girl, you gotta move your junk.
你爸想让你多陪陪他
I gotta get out of here. I gotta go see this girl, Tanya.
She lives on this side of town.
Yeah, go see Tanya. Good idea.
Okay, man, hey. I'm gonna be there, man. I want you guys to win!
Bye! Excelsior, Pat!
Excelsior! That's my man. Lets go!
橄榄球禁止入内  《蝇王》也不准
Pat. Patty.
别这样  你要干什么？ 我还没看完呢
- 关我屁事 - 你搞什么鬼？
你就这么扔外面了？
怎么了？你在我这不准看那些垃圾
你听我告诉你
《蝇王》是怎么回事  一个岛上有群小男孩
他们有个海螺  谁拿到海螺谁就能发号施令
要是你拿不到海螺
你就不能再发号施令了  有个小胖仔
Where have you been?
他们管他叫小猪  非常卑鄙  还有场谋杀
Huh?
人性本恶  哪有什么幸福线
We got a serious situation on our hands, you know that.
好强的梗概  可我还是得看
We gotta beat the Giants if we wanna have a chance of getting into
谁  什么  你跑到这来干什么？
the division, any chance of playing in the playoffs. Do you realize that?
只要你的两个指导医师中有一个丢了执照
I didn't realize that. Yeah, that's the bind we're in.
你的整个裁决就算玩完了
I mean, I think it would be wise if we spent father-son time, reading
你怎么知道我们在这的？
我去你爸妈家找你
他们说你来这了
丹尼  这是蒂芙尼  蒂芙尼  这是丹尼
about the Eagles, talking about them, just to strengthen the good
你好  帕特跟我说起过你
- 这就是信里说的那姑娘？- 是
luck thing that you're in.
他在信里提过我？ 那姑娘是说我？
Okay. Yeah? Right. Hmm?
- 没错  他提过你 - 他怎么说的？
他说你们俩在互相帮助  你人很好
还说你口无遮拦  不过…
接着说嘛  他信里还说我什么了
你想知道什么的话  我可以直接告诉你
没什么  那只是封很普通的信
- 不错嘛  她挺好的 - 她就是我那个f打头的朋友
I just wanted to, maybe I didn't, spend enough time with you growing
- 是大写的F - 指的是“朋友”
我能看看你们俩练的舞吗？
up. I spent too much time with your brother. It might have made you
没问题
feel worse about your behavior, but I didn't know anything, I didn't
know how to handle it.
- 就这样？ - 怎么？有什么问题
I mean, that's what all this Eagles stuff
- 介意我提点意见吗？ - 你说
is about. It's about us, spending time now. I wanna do everything I
- 确定？ - 说吧  说吧
- 你说吧 - 帕特  我觉得你应该面对蒂芙尼
我跳给你看  我给你演示一下
你应该对她表现得更有感情
你应该多摆胯
can to help you get back on your feet. That's the whole point. Yeah.
就像这个样子  帕特  像这样开始
你扭动的幅度可以更大些吗？
没错  就这样
幅度再大些
I wish you'd watch these games with me so we could talk, we could get into things.
你还可以转个圈  这样没问题的
很好  你跳得很不错
So would you, would you just come downstairs
- 好了  我们懂了 - 好吧
and talk to me and Randy now?
来吧  帕特  再投入点
Randy, tell him what I'm doing.
帕特  把脸涂黑
He's betting everything on the Giant game. Everything.
- 什么意思？ - 你懂的
All the money that he needs for the restaurant, he's betting on the Giant game.
等等  等等
Tell him why. Because he believes in you. Is that true?
我有办法了
I believe in you, Patty. I believe in you. I want you to know that.
来试试  帕特  来试试
So I'm gonna bet heavy on this game.
You understand? Yeah.
Heavy. I want you to go to the game with your brother.
You want me to go to the game with Jake?
曳步  曳步
Of course I do. Does he want me to go?
妹子  动作大点
Of course he wants you to go.
我得走了  要去见个叫塔尼娅的姑娘
He told you that? He told me, yes.
Even with all his friends? With all his friends. He trusts you.
她住附近
去见塔尼娅吧
He's not embarrassed?
我会去看的  你们一定要赢啊！
No. I'd love to go to the game, too, but as you know, I'm banned
再见  精进不休啊  帕特！
from the stadium. Cause I'd love to see us beat the Giants and take
- 精进不休！ - 这就对了  走了！
a lot of money from this asshole.
帕特  帕特
Listen, personally, I think it's a stupid bet. As a matter of fact,
I think it's ridiculous to bet all that dough for the restaurant on a game.
Randy.  I just hope you heard what I said. It's like a
family business, it's our family endeavor. We all stick together on this.
That's how it works. That's a positive, positive vibe.
I made a commitment to Tiffany about a project, and we have a very
你去哪了？
important part of it that we have to go over on Sunday, and
嗯？
现在局势很不妙
我们得打赢巨人队才有机会出线
it's good for me, Dad. It's making me disciplined and focused, and it's,
it's--, I never would've thought this, but it's a good thing.
才有机会打入季后赛  你想到没有？
What is this thing you're doing?
- 没想到 - 我们赌的就是这个
Yeah, what is it? What is this project, hon?
It's a dance thing, okay? There's nothing more to it, Dad. I swear.
我觉得我们父子应该多花点时间待在一起
一起读老鹰队的新闻  一起讨论
来增强你身上福气的力量
好吧
Listen, I need to ask you something.
Tomorrow can I spend half the day with you and half the day at the Eagles game?
I'm gonna pretend that you didn't just ask me that.
Why? These are the two days that you have promised me and that we have
prepared to nail the big move. It's not ready yet.
And we don't have a move yet.
I know, but my dad opened up to me and it was really beautiful and I
wanna be of service to him, okay? And he's worried that the juju from
我只是想…你小时候我没有多花时间陪你
the Eagles is being fucked up and he's concerned that it's because
我花了太多时间陪你哥
I'm spending time with you.
Oh, I messed up the Eagles' juju?
No, you're not messing up the juju, but the juju is messed up because
这可能让你变得不够自信
I'm not with him during the games.
我那时什么都不知道
Guess what? What?
我不知道该怎么处理
Nikki replied to your letter. But you can't read it until after
老鹰队的意义就在这里
是为了让我们能花更多时间相处
you nail the big move. Go.
我想尽我所能帮你康复  这才是全部意义
我希望你能跟我一起看这些比赛
这样我们就能一起聊天  彼此谅解
Tiff, I'm sorry. I can't do anything else without reading
Nikki's letter, okay? It's just--, it's in the back of my head.
We don't almost have it, all right?
I just hope you can handle it. Thank you.
你能不能下楼来
跟我和兰迪聊聊天？
What was her energy when she gave it to you?
兰迪  跟他说说我在干什么
She was intrigued, excited, and a little scared.
他把所有财产都赌在了跟巨人队的那场比赛上
She was scared? About what? Did she tell you?
他用来开餐馆的所有钱都赌在了那场比赛上
告诉他为什么
- 因为他相信你 - 真的吗？
Try to stay positive.
我相信你  帕特  我想让你明白这一点
I'm just gonna read it out loud, okay? Because if she says anything
所以我这次赌得很大
that's, you know, is that too much to ask?
- 懂吗？ - 懂
No.
赌得很大  我想让你跟你哥一起去看比赛
你想让我跟杰克一起去看比赛？
I thought you were gonna read it out loud.
- 当然 - 他想让我去吗？
他当然想让你去
Okay. Sorry.
- 他这么跟你说的？ - 他说的
"Dear Pat,
- 他的朋友们也去？ - 他们都去  他信任你
It was very emotional for me to get your letter, as I'm
他不觉得难为情？
不  我也想去的 不过你知道我被禁止入场了
sure you can imagine, but I'm glad you took the risk of discreetly
getting it to me through Tiffany.
我想亲眼看见我们打败巨人队
然后从这个混球手里赢一大笔钱
This gives us a chance to communicate while I keep the restraining order until I feel safe.
要我说  这个赌实在是太蠢了
事实上
I must admit you sound terrific and I'm happy that you are
把开餐厅的所有钱都赌上去简直不可理喻
feeling so positive and becoming a more loving and caring man, which I
兰迪  我希望你听懂我的话了
always knew you were.
这就像是笔家庭生意
我们全家人一起努力  一起坚持下去
就是这样  这就是一种积极的力量
我答应了蒂芙尼完成一项任务
I was moved to read about Excelsior' and your
我们星期天有个很重要的环节要完成
belief in happy endings. I am also moved by your act of love to read
the books I have taught at the high school. I'm sorry you find them so
negative, but I disagree. I think they are great works of art that
这对我很有好处  爸
reflect how hard life can be and they can also help kids prepare
这让我变得更有条理  更专注
我以前从没这么想过  但这是件好事
themselves for the hardness of life. In spite of all these
positive developments, Pat, I have to say if it's me reading the
究竟是什么事？
什么事  是什么任务？
signs, I need to see something to prove you are ready to resume our
是跳舞  只是单纯的跳舞  我发誓没别的
marriage. Otherwise I find myself thinking that we might both be
better off moving on with our lives separately.
Please don't react quickly
我有件事要问你
to this, but take time to think about it.
明天我能不能半天陪你  半天看老鹰队的比赛？
I'm glad you're doing so well. Love, Nikki. ?
我就当你没问过
- 为什么？ - 你答应过我这两天
要练习那个那个绝招的  我们还没练好
我们还没想好是什么动作呢
我知道  但我爸对我敞开了心扉  我很感动
I think I'm done for today, okay?
我想为他做点什么 他担心老鹰队的好运被破坏了
She said to show her something,
他觉得这是因为
我跟你待在一起
那是我坏了老鹰队的好运喽？
Pat. This dance can be that something. You would have never
不是你坏了好运  是我没跟他一起看比赛
done something like this in a million years. It shows all kinds
好运才没了
of skills on so many different levels: focus, collaboration,
- 你猜怎么着？ - 怎么？
尼基回信了
discipline. It's romantic, like I said it would be. It's for her.
但是没搞定那个绝招就不准看信  开始吧
Thanks for the letter. I'll see you tomorrow, okay?
Can I use your phone? Is it an emergency?
Yeah, kind of. What kind of emergency?
蒂芙尼  对不起  不看信我什么也做不好
这事在我脑子里  一直挥之不去
Well, I'm just doing this project with Tiffany and I wanted to tell
要不然我们什么也弄不出来
her I'm not gonna be on time.
- 但愿你能接受 - 谢谢
Just don't make her an emergency, that crazy girl, you know?
She's not crazy -- I'll just borrow Jake's phone. It's too bad you
她给你的时候心情怎么样？
can't come in to the stadium, but I know you were kicked out, you know,
她很好奇  很兴奋  还有点害怕
for beating everybody up. Guess we're not that different, huh, Dad?
害怕什么  她告诉你没有？
That a bad thing?
No, I think, it's a good thing.
别太失望
Don't drink too much. Don't hit anybody. You'll be fine.
Yeah. I'm solid.
我大声读出来可以吗？ 要是她写了什么
你懂的  这要求过分吗？
没有
This is my little brother Pat.
Hey, how you doing?
So, Pat, what's this I hear about you just gettin' out?
Yeah, from the looney bin!
What the fuck?! I talked to you about that already!
你不是要大声读出来吗
好吧  抱歉
I told you guys- It's all right.
亲爱的帕特
Huh? No. It's alright.
收到你的来信我十分感动
He's a good dude! He's a good dude.
Oh, shit! The Asian invasion!
但我很高兴你甘愿冒险
让蒂芙尼把信捎给我
They're here every week! No!
这既让我们有机会交流
又没有违反你的人身限制令  让我很安心
我必须承认你听起来很好
我很高兴你如此乐观
Uh, Jake you better get your brother.
变得更加体贴  更有同情心
Cuckoo bird's takin' off. Doctor Patel!
我一直都清楚  这才是你的本色
Pat! Hey! What are you doing here?
You know, we must beat the Giants, my brother.
I'm not supposed to be seeing you,
right? Outside the office?
Pat, Pat. That's illegal!
Pat, today I'm your brother in green, not your therapist. I'm so
happy to see you. How wonderful that you are here!
你所说的“精进不休”
Hey, Jake this is Cliff. This is my doctor, Cliff.
还有你对美满结局的信念让我很感动
Look, two things. We gotta watch that bubble screen for fuckin'
你读了我在高中教的那些书
Manning in the backfield and we gotta make sure we knock the
这个举动太有爱了  我也很感动
很遗憾你觉得它们写得太悲观
receivers on their ass on the line of scrimmage.
但我不同意  我觉得它们都是伟大的艺术作品
You can say that again. Those cocksuckers!
反映了人生的艰辛
能帮助孩子们为未来的人生做好准备
尽管有这些好的进展  帕特
我不得不说  如果换做是我
我需要确定你已经做好准备和我破镜重圆
否则的话  我觉得
我们还是分开旅行的好
请不要草率回信
Okay, you know what? I don't have her phone number. If you want, if
好好考虑一阵子
you really want, you can call Veronica cause she does, but I
很高兴你过得不错  爱你的  尼基
don't want to talk to Veronica.
Why don't you wanna talk to Veronica?
Because she brings me down, man! She just brings me down.
You have to change. You're not gonna throw the marriage away.
There's some kind of love there. I know, I used to see it.
You guys have a beautiful thing that got broken somewhere along the
line and you gotta fix it like a chiropractor.
今天就到这  行吗？
You gotta give it a chiropractic adjustment.
Enough with awkwardness! I don't wanna walk in your house and not be
able to say what I wanna say.
她说要你证明给她看
You're right, man. You're right, you're right,
Eagles, baby! Yeah! Let's go! What the fuck? What's that smell?
这个舞就是个机会
你以前根本就不可能做到
这能表现你的
注意力  协作能力和条理性
Nasty Indian curry! This is America, baby! Go back to your country!
What, what's wrong? Hey!
很浪漫  就像我说过的那样  是为她而做的
Whoa, whoa, what's going on? Stay back, Pat. Stay back.
Leave the fucking Indians alone. Stay here, stay here!
谢谢你帮我捎信  明天见
I'm not gonna go anywhere. Don't get in a fight!
I'm not gonna fight. I'm not gonna fight.
Hey, not my brother! Hey, hey, hey!
Break it up or you'll be arrested!
- 手机借我一下行吗？ - 要紧事？
- 算是吧 - 什么事？
我答应了蒂芙尼要跟她练舞
得告诉她我要迟点去
别拿那个疯姑娘当回事
她不是疯子…我借杰克的手机好了
你不能进场真是太遗憾了
但我知道你是因为打架才被赶出来的
What'd you do? What happened? Dad-
看来我们也没什么两样  对吧？
What the fuck happened? Dad.
这算是坏事吗？
The birds lose, I lose a fuckin' fortune, a fortune to Randy!
不  我倒觉得是件好事
What the fuck did you do?! You fucking lost it!
别喝太多酒  别跟人打架  就不会有事了
I thought you said you had it together! You were solid!
我清醒得很
I am solid. I was solid at the game, Dad.
I'm solid, I'm solid now.
You fell apart! What are you fucking talking about?!
Your son was trying to-
这是帕特  我弟
It's all fucking ruined now. It's all ruined.
你好吗？
No, Dad! It's all fucking ruined now! It's all fucking ruined!
帕特  我听说你刚被放出来啊？
No, Dad, Dad, Dad, don't!
刚从疯人院出来呢！
It's all ruined, you little fucking shit!
搞什么鬼？我都说了别提这个
No, Dad! I didn't do a fucking thing! Come on, Dad!
You loser! You loser!
- 我说了… - 没关系
I'm not a loser.
You fucking loser! You ruined everything!
没关系
He was defending his brother!
好兄弟！
You fucking idiot! You spike the ball on the one yard line,
该死！黄祸来了！
Who is this?! Who's this?!
- 他们每个礼拜都来！ - 不是吧
We need to talk right now! When you make a serious commitment to
somebody, it is not cool to not show up!
Wait a second, I tried to call, my God, what's happening,
I called--, but I tried to call you, Tiffany, I-
Oh, really? Yes.
I told you I was gonna split my time with my dad and you, and my
杰克  看好你弟
dad was pulling me in one direction. Doctor Patel, Ronnie-
- 布谷鸟要起飞了 - 帕特尔医生！
Well, that sounds great, Pat. That's great for all of them, but
all of them didn't make a commitment to me in return for my help.
- 帕特！ - 你怎么也来了？
我们必须得击败巨人队嘛
I'm Tiffany, by the way.
我是不是不该…
在办公室外面跟你见面的？
- 帕特  帕特 - 这是违法的
What is this craziness with Tiffany Maxwell?
帕特  今天我就是你的同盟军
There's no craziness. I told you who she was,
不是你的心理医生
I was doing this thing with her. We had a conversation!
真高兴见到你  你来了真是太好了！
She's fucking nuts! When you started spending time with her,
杰克  这是克里夫  我的医生克里夫
it all fell apart. This is the fucking reason right here.
注意两件事  一件是那帮草包后卫的部署
You think I fucked up the Eagles' juju, don't you?
另一件  在比赛开始至死球期间
Ever since, ever since he was with you, ever since-
我们就得把他们的接球手打得屁股开花
You think that I'm why today's happened?
再说一遍吧  那帮狗杂种！
That's right, you are why today happened.
I'm the reason why today happened?
I think so. Let's talk about that.
Be my guest.
The first night that Pat and I met at my sister's, the Eagles beat the
Forty Niners handily, forty to twenty-six. The second time we got
together we went for a run and the Phillies beat the Dodgers seven to
five in the NLCS.
She's right, Dad.
The next time we went for a run the Eagles beat the Falcons, twenty-
seven to fourteen.
Wow.
The third time we got together we had Raisin Bran in the diner and
the Phillies dominated Tampa Bay in the fourth game of the World
Series, ten to two.
我没有她的号码
Oh, wow.
你要是真想找她的话  可以打给维罗妮卡
Let me think about that. Wait a minute.
Well, why don't you think about when the Eagles beat the Seahawks,
但我不想跟维罗妮卡说话
fourteen to seven.
你为什么不跟维罗妮卡说话？
He was with you? He was with me. We went for a run.
因为她让我觉得心烦！ 她只会让我心烦
Really? That's crazy.
你不能再这样了  不能对婚姻置之不理
There have been no games since Pat and I have been rehearsing every
你们之间明明是有爱意的  我以前看的出来
day and if Pat had been with me like he was supposed to, he
你们的感情明明很好  只是不知哪里出了问题
wouldn't have gotten in a fight, he wouldn't be in trouble, maybe the
你得把它修复好  就像个按摩师一样
把其中错位的地方矫正好
Eagles beat the New York Giants.
别再顾着面子了！ 我可不想去你家的时候
She's making a lot of sense, Pop. That's all right on all counts.
想说什么都不敢说出口
你说得没错  你说得没错
Does anybody here happen to know what the official motto of the
老鹰队必胜！我们上吧！ 搞什么鬼？
state of New York is on the official seal of the State of New York?
什么鬼气味？
Huh? Anybody? Do you? Do you know?
臭烘烘的印度咖喱味  这儿是美国！
Excelsior. ?Look it up. Yeah, Excelsior. ?Oh Pat.
滚回你们自己国家去！
怎么了？
Not that I give a fuck about football or about your
- 怎么回事？ - 别过来  帕特  别过来
superstitions, but if it's me reading the signs, I don't send the
Eagles guy whose personal motto is Excelsior, ?to a fucking Giants
- 别管那些该死的印度佬 - 呆在这  呆在这！
game, especially when he's already in a legal situation.
- 我哪都不去 - 别打架！
Unbelievable. Wow. How did you know all that stuff?
我不要打架  我不要打架
I did my research. Well, I gotta say, I'm impressed.
别碰我哥！
Thank you.
快停手  不然你们就要被捕了！
I gotta rethink this whole thing. I didn't trust it before,
but I gotta say, now I do.
Oh, now you like her, Dad? I have to say I do. Yup.
Patrizio, I feel terrible, you know? You made the bet, I won a lot
of money, and now look, your whole family is in turmoil.
Oh, fuck off, Randy. You love it. You live for this shit. You've been
- 你怎么了？发生什么事了？ - 爸
betting against my father for years.
Is that right?
You're twisting the knife right now. You get off on it!
- 这他妈怎么回事？ - 爸
That's bullshit! That's not true! Don't say that!
老鹰输了  我输了一大笔钱给兰迪！
You get off on it! If not, then prove it. Prove it.
Yeah, prove it, prove it!
你他妈搞什么鬼？！全搞砸了！
How do you want me to prove it? How's he gonna prove it?
By giving them the chance to win back everything, double or nothing.
你不是说你很镇定吗！你走的时候还很清醒！
我很清醒  比赛的时候我很清醒
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
现在也很清醒
Double or nothing on the Bengals, next week? Is that what you're saying?
你明明就没控制住！还讲什么鬼话？！
他尽力了…
现在全完了  全完了
- 爸  别这样！ - 全完了！
Against the Cowboys.
爸  爸  别这样！
That's your team isn't it, Randy? That's his team!
全完了  都怪你这个混蛋！
爸！我没做错什么！搞清楚！
你个废物！
I know who his team is. When is the game?
我不是废物
December twenty-eight, last game of the season.
你个废物！你把什么都搞砸了！
Oh, my God. Same day as the Benjamin Franklin
他是为了救他哥哥！
你个白痴！居然在一码线上掷地球
Pairs Open Freestyle Dance Competition.
Oh God. Randy, I thought they were America's Team.
- 是谁？ - 是谁？
Don't you believe in America's Team?
我们得谈谈  你一本正经地做了保证
Yeah, Randy, don't you believe in America's Team?
Yeah, I believe in America's Team but if I win that bet, I win your
结果却放我鸽子  实在太逊了！
- 听我说  我本来是想打电话给你 - 怎么回事？
book, you're out of action, you get no restaurant, no nothing.
我真准备打给你的  蒂芙尼…
I like it. No. No, Patrizio-
- 真的吗？ - 真的
我跟你说过了  我要分一半时间给我爸
我爸拉着我这一边  帕特尔医生  罗尼…
I believe in the Eagles, I believe in my son,
这借口不错  全是他们的错
I'll take the action. I'll take it.
Dad! Patrizio, don't! It's toxic!
但他们可没承诺要报答我
I have faith, I have faith. Excelsior belongs in this house-
Dad- --not in the State of New York. In this house.
对了  我叫蒂芙尼
Dad, listen to me. I didn't know that Excelsior?was the state
motto of New York, okay?
这个蒂芙尼・麦克斯维尔到底有什么毛病？
I didn't know, either, but now I know.
I know, but listen to me, this is toxic. Dad, Dad, Dad, this is
toxic, you shouldn't be doing this, you shouldn't be doing-
她没有毛病  我告诉过你了
Randy, what do you say--
这是我跟她之间的问题  我们在商量呢！
Be quiet, shut up. You already did enough. Randy, what do you say?
她就是个疯子！自从你跟她待在一起后
My birds, Benjamin Franklin's team favored by one and a half points.
问题就层出不穷  这全是她的错
I 'll give you three more.
你觉得是我坏了老鹰队的好运  是吧？
Patrizio, stop it! And Randy, don't you take the bet!
自从他碰到你之后…
In fact, I'll give you ten points. No, Dad! Dad!
你觉得今天的事都是我造成的？
Dad! You have to take that bet on the Cowboys.
没错  都是你造成的
我就是那个祸根？
- 没错 - 我们谈谈吧
洗耳恭听
Dolores, would you stop him? Jesus!
我跟帕特第一次在我姐姐家见面的那天晚上
How could you not take that bet? Even with the ten points I give
老鹰队轻松击败了49人队  40比26
you, that's an insane spread to your advantage. Cowboys are
第二次  我们一起跑步
cowards. And I'll bet you're such a coward, you won't take the ten.
老鹰队在国联冠军赛上以7比5击败了道奇队
Plus, are you listening, plus whatever their score is at the
爸  她说得没错
我们下一次跑步的时候  老鹰队击败了隼鹰队
dance thing. What's that? Tiffany, what's that?
27比14
What? No, no, no, no. You're crazy to give away that many
第三次  我们晚餐去吃了提子麦麸
points. That's ridiculous! I won't take that!
However, wait a second. I do like the idea of a parlay.
老鹰队在第四场世界联赛上10比2
大胜坦帕湾
What? No parlay! No! No, don't do it. Don't do it.
慢着  让我想想
你怎么不想想  老鹰队14比7
击败海鹰队的时候
Pat, how do they run this dance competition?
- 他跟你在一起？ - 他跟我在一起  我们去跑步了
I mean, how do they score it and everything?
真的吗？太神了
I don't know, I don't know how they fucking score! We're participating.
我跟帕特排练以来一直都没有比赛
We're not, we're not a part of it. There are people, this is a high-
要是今天帕特像他答应的那样跟我在一起的话
end dance contest. I don't know. Do not put it as part of the parlay,
他就不会打架  不会惹麻烦
Randy. Don't- They go by the Philadelphia rules.
没准老鹰队还会击败纽约巨人队
Each dancer is scored on a scale of one to ten, ten being the highest.
爸  她说得很有道理  所有比分都是对的
You have to average the four judges' scores.
Okay, score is from one to ten, right? And you guys are how good?
有人知道纽约州纪念邮戳上印的
We suck. We don't suck. Pat's a beginner,
纽约州官方格言是什么吗？
I'm okay, we're happy just to be going there.
有人知道吗  你知道吗  你呢？
And how are the people you're competing against?
- “精进不休” 不信的话自己去查 - 帕特
They're good. Some of them are professionals.
They're good? Better than you? A lot better.
A lot better. So if I was to say you only have to score five,
我才不在乎橄榄球  还有你们那些迷信
I would be really very generous, right?
但如果换做是我  我绝不会让一个
No, no, that would be amazing if we got five. Let's not get away-
拿“精进不休”当座右铭的球迷去看巨人队比赛
Oh, come on, we can get a five out of ten!
Gimme a break! Gimme me a break!
更何况他还背着官司
We can't get five! Give em a five. Give em a five.
- 不可思议 - 你怎么会知道这些东西？
We can do a five.
What are you talking about, Dad? You haven't even seen us dance!
That's the parlay.
- 我做了很多功课 - 不得不说  这很有说服力
Will somebody please explain to me the parlay? Please?
You gotta win two bets or you lose the whole thing. For Pat Sr. to
win, the birds gotta beat the Cowboys plus Pat and Tiffany gotta
谢谢
get at least a five at the dance.
我得把整件事重新想一下  我以前还不信这一套
That's very, very manic indeed. That's the parlay. Shake on it.
但现在信了
You know what? I'm not gonna be a part of this.  Randy,
- 那你现在喜欢她了吧？ - 不得不说  是的
Randy, you're a sickness. You're a fucking sickness, Randy. I'm out.
帕吉欧  我很内疚  是你设的赌局
Pat, you can't quit. I'm not doing the dance. I'm out.
Pat, calm down. Thank about it. See you later.
我赢了一大笔钱  可你家现在却闹得一团糟
Pat, no. What are you doing?
滚你的  兰迪  你明明就开心死了
Pat. I'm out.
巴不得发生这种破事呢
Here we are again at the one yard line. DeSean, snatching defeat from
你跟我爸打赌打了好几年了
真的吗？
你现在说这些狗屁  你爽死了好么！
the jaws of victory. There you go.
一派胡言！不是这样的！别胡说！
What does that even mean, Dad? I'm not gonna make that, that, that
你就是爽死了！不然的话  你证明一下啊
connection that you're making with DeSean Jackson. It doesn't matter
没错  证明一下
- 你要我怎么证明？ - 他要怎么证明？
anymore okay? Just because I have the fucking jersey on...
再赌一次  给他们一个机会赢回一切
I'm not gonna do it. I'm sorry.
You are not a stand up guy right now. If it's me reading the
signs... if it's me reading the signs-
要么加倍  要么勾销
不行  不行
If it's you reading the signs? You're reading the signs? Oh, okay.
赌下个礼拜跟孟加拉虎队的比赛
要么加倍  要么勾销
你指的是这个吗？
Pat! You are not a stand up guy!
是跟牛仔队打
- 那不是你支持的队吗  兰迪？ - 那是他的队！
Pat! I told you not to push it.
- 我知道他支持的是哪个队 - 哪天比赛？
Yeah, but he's gotta do this thing. He can't be a quitter.
He cannot be a quitter.
12月28号  这个赛季最后一场比赛
You took that stupid parlay thing, and now he won't do the dance and
- 天哪 - 跟富兰克林酒店的
双人自由舞比赛同一天
it was very constructive for him, and you ruined it.
There's only one way to get him to show.
兰迪  他们可是美国之队啊
What's that? Oh, what's that?
难道你不相信美国之队吗？
We have to tell him Nikki's gonna be there.
对啊  兰迪  难道你不相信美国之队吗？？
我当然相信美国之队  但要是我赢了
你们就完蛋了  餐厅也没了  什么都没了
- 有意思 - 不行  帕吉欧
我相信老鹰队  相信我儿子
这个赌我打
- 爸！ - 帕吉欧  不行  这是在赌命！
We have to tell him that she's going.
我有信心  我有信心 精进不休属于我们家
But that's a lie! It's a white lie.
It's a white lie, what's that matter? That's no big deal.
而不是纽约州
So it's a little lie. There's no other way.
爸  听我说  我以前不知道“精进不休”
You know, we gotta leave a trail of bread crumbs so that
是纽约州格言
我以前也不知道  但我现在知道了
he can live his life without ruining it.
我知道  但听我说  这是在赌命  爸
No. I don't approve. You can't do it.
这是在赌命  你不能这么做  你不能这么做
兰迪  你意下如何…
闭嘴  你说得够多了 兰迪  你意下如何？
Well, you know, I didn't approve when you called her and you told
我的小鹰  富兰克林之队 领先1.5分
her where he was running, so she could ambush him. I didn't approve
我再让你3分
帕吉欧  够了！兰迪  别打这个赌！
of that, but you did it anyway, so I'm doing this anyway. That's it.
- 我要让你10分 - 不  爸！
We're gonna tell him Nikki'll be there.
- 爸！ - 你必须把赌注押在牛仔队上
You gotta be part of it. We have to do it.
- 多洛蕾丝  还不快拦着他？ - 天啊！
你怎么能不打这个赌？我可让了你10分
Aren't you nervous to be lying?
这对你来说可是个天大的便宜
Yeah. A little bit. But it's for the best.
牛仔队都是懦夫  你也是  让你10分都不敢
再加上  听好了  加上他们在舞蹈比赛的得分
什么比赛来着  蒂芙尼  叫什么？
?.. but if it was me reading the signs... . ?
- 什么？ 不行 - 你让那么多分真是疯了
太荒唐了！这个我不同意！
不过  连赌的赌法倒是不错
- 什么  连赌可不行！ - 不  别这么做
帕特  这个舞蹈比赛是怎么比的？
我是说  分数是怎么算的？
我不知道  我怎么知道他们怎么算分数的！
我们只是参赛者
又不是组织者  这个比赛很高端的
我不知道  别把这个算进赌局里
- 兰迪  别… - 按照费城惯例
每对舞者按1到10打分  10分最高
That's it. Okay.
算四位评委的平均分
好  按1到10打分是吧？你们水平怎么样？
- 逊毙了 - 我们不差  帕特初学
我还凑合  能参加比赛已经很不错了
你们对手的水平怎么样？
他们很棒  有的还是专业的
- 他们很厉害？比你们强？ - 强得多
强很多  那我要是说  你们只要拿到5分就行了
算是相当客气了吧？
Hey.
不行  不行  我们要是能得5分简直就是奇迹
说回正题吧…
拜托  我们5分总还是拿得到的！
Hey, what's up?
饶了我吧！饶了我吧！
- 我们不可能拿到5分！ - 就赌5分吧
我们当然能拿到5分
Sorry I'm late.
爸  你说什么呢？你压根没见过我们跳舞！
It's fine.
这才叫连赌嘛
谁行行好  给我解释一下  什么叫连赌？
要么两局皆赢  要么全盘皆输
老帕要是想赢  不光老鹰得打败牛仔
帕特和蒂芙尼还得在比赛中至少得到5分
- 这真的太疯狂了 - 这就叫连赌
握手成交
我不会掺和这件事的
兰迪  你真是个小人  我不干了
- 帕特  你不能退出 - 我不参加了
- 拜拜了 - 帕特  冷静点  好好想想
- 帕特  不行 - 你要干什么？
- 帕特 - 我不干了
我们又站在了一码线上
德肖恩就是在这里一时失手
功败垂成  你现在也是这样
爸  这又算什么？
不要拿我跟德肖恩・杰克逊比  这是两码事
我穿了他的球衣不代表…
我不干了  对不起
你这也太不讲义气了  如果换做是我
如果换做是我…
如果换做是你？换做是你？好吧
帕特！你太不讲义气了！
我告诉过你  不要逼他的
可他必须得参加  他不能半途而废
他不能半途而废
都怪你要搞那个愚蠢的连赌  他都不愿意跳舞了
那对他很有好处的  全被你毁了
Come on, it's gonna be great.
要让他参加比赛  只有一个办法
Nikki's gonna be there. You know? Everything's gonna come together.
- 什么办法？ - 什么？
我们得告诉他  尼基会去看
It's what's meant to be. You okay?
Don't get wobbly on me. I'm not.
We have a dance to do. We have a parlay. You gotta stay focused.
I'm focused. Okay, let's go.
- 她不可能去的 - 我们得告诉他她会去
我们必须得告诉他她会去
- 这是在骗他！ - 可这是为他好
这是为他好  有什么关系？没什么大不了
- 只是撒个小谎而已 - 没别的办法了
我们得给他留下一线希望
他才不至于把自己这一辈子毁掉
Look at the dancers. You see them? Shit.
我不同意  你们不能这么做
你要打电话给她  告诉她他在哪跑步
Hey, Randy, Jake. What do we got?
她好埋伏在那的时候  我也不同意
Dallas just tied with another field goal, three-three.
I'm worried about the bet.
可你还是那么做了  这回我也一样  就这么办
Don't worry about the bet. I'm worried about the bet.
Holy shit.
我们要告诉他尼基会去
Is this Dancing with the Stars?
- 你不能戳穿 - 我们非这样做不可
Well, you knew that. Maybe you should've scouted em.
Look at those fucking dancers!
你撒谎的时候会紧张吗？
You can give me the money now, you know?
有点吧  但也只能如此了
Patty, Patty, all we have to do is we have to make a five.
That's all. You stay here and watch the game with me.
The birds are better when Pat is with me. We settled that.
Relax, we're gonna do fine, okay? I'll see you in a little bit.
“但如果换做是我…”
I'll see you up there, okay? Okay.
Hey, Pat, Tiffany!
Hey. What a glorious, beautiful occasion, man.
Yeah, yeah. All right, buddy, I'll see you. Alright.
Wish me luck, man.
Excelsior!
Wait, what's this?
What? I thought you were doing it.
Oh, I thought you were doing it. We're doing a dance thing anyway
for God's sake.
I want you to remember everything. I want you to remember all of the
good stuff that we have here.
Of course I do. Just check in. I gotta go find Veronica.
就这样吧
Hi, good evening. Evening.
Check in? How many dancers are there?
What?! Nikki? Nikki.
Oh, Jesus.
你好
What the fuck?
你好吗？
Sweetie, sweetie. Honey, calm down.
You're killing me. You're killing me!
不好意思  我迟到了
Tiffany, please. She'll see how well he's doing,
没关系
maybe she'll lift the restraining order.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
Pat told me. He told me you should never throw a marriage
out the window.
Pat did not say that. He didn't say that.
He said it several times, Tiffany, and this is his chance.
You gotta give him a chance.
Bartender! Bartender, can I get a vodka, please?
So, you want another one? Sure.
一定会很棒的
尼基会去  你知道吗？一切都要好起来了
这是注定的  你没事吧？
- 别魂不守舍的 - 我没有
我们有场舞要跳  还有个赌要打呢  专心点
- 我很专心 - 好  我们走
- 看看那一对  看见没有？ - 完了
兰迪  杰克  情况怎么样？
达拉斯又得了1分  打平了  3比3
我很担心这个赌
- 别担心 - 我很担心
神啊
So what do you do? I'm a lawyer. Litigator, actually.
这是“与星共舞”吗？
你事先干嘛不侦察好他们的实力
Oh, the arguing kind.
瞧那些选手跳的多好啊！
And the scores for Santos and Aguilar are: seven point six, seven point three, seven point four, and
你现在就可以把钱给我了
six point nine for an average score of seven point three.
帕特  我们只要拿到5分就行了
你待在这陪我看比赛
Three, two, one! Philadelphia beats Dallas! They are on their way to the playoffs.
帕特跟我在一起时老鹰打得更好
别担心  我们会做好的  一会见
- 你到那去找我  好吗？ - 好
你们好  帕特  蒂芙尼！
这场面可真隆重啊
兄弟  一会儿见
祝我好运
精进不休！
Where's Tiffany?
I don't know, Mom. Have you seen her?
这是怎么回事？
You gotta find her. I know, Mom, I know.
什么？我以为是你先牵的
我以为是你先牵的  反正我们等会儿要跳舞
我希望你能记住这一切  我希望你能记住
我们现在拥有的一切美好的东西
- 我当然记得 - 去签到吧  我去找维罗妮卡
- 你们  晚上好 - 晚上好
- 签到？ - 有多少选手参赛？
Hey, WHAT are you doing? She's fine, buddy, she's with me.
She's fine? Yeah.
什么？！尼基？是尼基
Why don't you shut up, okay? How many drinks have you had?
I've had two vodkas. Listen, I don't know what choices
you've made, but you gotta deal with it right now, okay? We're in this.
天哪
We're in what?
Next, Pat Solatano and Tiffany Maxwell.
You know, I used to think that you were the best thing that ever
happened to me, but now I think that you might maybe be the worst
thing and I'm sorry that I ever met you.
Good for you.
And the scores for Makarov and Tretiak are: six point seven, eight
搞什么鬼？
亲爱的  亲爱的  宝贝儿  冷静
point one, seven point five and six point five for an average score of
我恨你  我恨你！
蒂芙尼  她要是看到他恢复得多好
说不定就会取消限制令了
seven point two.
天哪  天哪
帕特对我说过  他说你永远也不该
放弃一段婚姻
They were great and they only got a seven point two.
帕特没这么说过  他没这么说过
他说过好多次  蒂芙尼  这对他来说是大好机会
This is a tough room.
你得给他一个机会
Got it.
Up next, ladies and gentlemen please welcome Pat Solatano, Jr. and Tiffany Maxwell.
Damn. Let's go, Patty! Come on, Pat!
酒保！酒保  来杯伏特加
- 再来一杯？ - 好
- 你是做什么的？ - 我是个律师  诉讼律师
就是跟人辩论的那种
7.6分  7.3分  7.4分
6.9分  平均分是7.3分
3  2  1  费城击败了达拉斯
他们即将进入季后赛
蒂芙尼呢？
不知道  妈  你看见她没有？
- 你得找到她 - 我知道  妈  我知道
- 你在干什么？ - 她没事的  她跟我一起的
- 她没事？ - 是啊
你就不能闭嘴吗  你喝了多少酒？
Alright, let's see the scores for Solatano and Maxwell.
- 两杯伏特加 - 我不知道你是不是改了主意
We have a four point nine, four eight, a four nine...
但你别胡闹  我们是一伙的
我们是一伙什么？
下一组  帕特・索拉塔诺和蒂芙尼・麦克斯维尔
That's really too bad, guys. That's a lot of fours.
我曾以为  遇见你是我这辈子最幸运的事
... and and a five point four for an average score of. . five point zero.
但现在  我觉得这是最倒霉的一件事
真希望我们从没见过
Sorry about that, guys.
真有你的
马卡洛夫和特莉迪亚克的得分是6.7分
Dad, Dad, did the Eagles win?
8.1分  7.5分  和6.5分  平均分为
The Eagles won, forty-four-six! They won, forty- four-six!
Come on!
7.2分
Why are they so excited about a five?
他们跳得那么好  居然只有7.2分
竞争真激烈
拿着
女士们  先生们  下面有请
小帕特・索拉塔诺和蒂芙尼・麦克斯维尔
帕特  加油！
How are you? You okay? Good. How are you? I'm really good. Yeah, thanks.
You looked really happy out there. Did I?
Yeah. Yeah, who'd have thought, dancing?
You look incredible. Thank you.
You lost a lot of weight. I've been reading your books and,
I have a positive attitude. I'm on medication, I'm in therapy.
Where's Tiffany? She left. What do you mean, she left?
She left. What do you think! Where is she?
Let me tell you, I know you don't wanna listen to your father,
I didn't listen to mine but I'm telling you, you gotta pay
attention to the signs. When life reaches out with a moment like
this, it's a sin if you don't reach back. I'm telling you, it's a sin
if you don't reach back, and it'll haunt you for the rest of your days
like a curse. You're facing a big challenge in your life right now,
at this very moment, right here. That girl loves you, she really
loves you. And I don't know if Nikki ever did, but she sure as
hell doesn't love you right now. I'm telling you, don't fuck this up.
I love you, Dad.
Hey! Would you just leave me alone?!
Wait a second! I have one more letter for you to read, okay?
What the fuck is the matter with you? Give it to her yourself!
Let me say something. You don't ever have to see me again if you
just read it, alright?
This is so fucked up. Yeah, just read it.
Dear Tiffany...
?.. I know you wrote the letter.
The only way you could meet my crazy... . ?
?.. was by doing something crazy yourself. Thank you.
I love you.
I knew it the minute I met you. I'm sorry it took so long for me to
catch up. I just got stuck. Pat. ?
索拉塔诺和麦克斯维尔的得分
4.9分  4.8分  4.9分
I wrote that a week ago.
You wrote that a week ago? Yes, I did.
太糟了  这么多4分
You let me lie to you for a week? I was trying to be romantic.
5.4分
You love me? Yeah, I do.
平均分为5.0分
Okay.
爸  老鹰赢了吗？
老鹰赢了  44比6！他们赢了  44比6！
休息10分钟  5分值得这样吗？
The world will break your heart ten ways to Sunday, that's guaranteed.
And I can't begin to explain that- -or the craziness inside myself and
everybody else, but guess what? Sunday is my favorite day again.
I think of everything everyone did for me and I feel like --a very lucky guy.
- 你好吗？ - 很好  你呢？
我很好  谢谢
- 你刚才看上去真的很开心 - 是吗？
We have to beat the Vikings by three. I'm givin' you a six, which
- 是的 - 是啊  谁想得到我还能跳舞呢？
is very generous after the beating you just took. So what are we
doin', what are we talkin' about here?
- 你看上去好极了 - 谢谢
I'd like to do another parlay if we make it to the next round, that's all.
But we are gonna make it to the next round. We're gonna beat...
- 你瘦了很多 - 我一直在读你的书
No, that was me that did that. No that was me.
我态度很积极  在吃药  还在看心理医生
That was me. I played the Jack. So you put the bread crumbs, the
garlic in the steak and you roll it up with the toothpicks?
Yeah. For, oh, maybe three hours, plus.
Everything's good, everything's good, yeah. I got you, you're all
down.  No, Randy, he's complaining. You know he lost a lot
of money. He's moaning and groaning. The restaurant's
happening because of Randy, so everything's good.
idztette: P53Killer
Created By : Usman Title : Silver inings Playbook http://www.facebook.com/usman.zubair5
- 蒂芙尼呢？ - 她走了
什么  她走了？
- 走了就是走了  你想什么呢！ - 她去哪儿了？
听我说  我知道你不想听你老爸的话
我以前也不听我老爸的话  但你听着
当生命在这样一个时刻给你发出信号时
你如果不回应  那就是罪过  给我听好
你如果不回应  就像个诅咒
你整个余生都会为之后悔
你人生中的一个重大转折此刻就在你眼前
就在此时此刻那个姑娘爱上你了
我不知道尼基到底有没有爱过你
但她现在肯定已经不爱你了
你给我听着  这次别再搞砸了
爸  我爱你
你别管我  行吗？
等等！我还有封信要给你看
你他妈什么毛病？自己递给她啊！
听我说  只要你读了这封信
就再也不用见到我了  行吗？
- 真是胡闹 - 你读就是了
亲爱的蒂芙尼…
我知道那封信是你写的
唯一能与我的疯狂相匹配的…
就是你也在做同样疯狂的事  谢谢你
我爱你
从我第一眼看见你就意识到了
很抱歉我花了这么久才想明白
我只是陷入过去了  帕特
我一个礼拜前写的
- 你一个礼拜前写的？ - 是的
你任由我骗了你一个礼拜？
我觉得这样比较浪漫
- 你爱我？ - 是的
好吧
生活会将你的心彻底击碎  这是肯定的
我无法解释这一点
也无法解释在我和其他所有人内心的疯狂
但你猜怎么着？星期天又成了我最爱的一天
我想到了每个人为我做的一切  我觉得很幸运
我们得赢维京队3分  我让你6分
- 这相当慷慨了 - 这是怎么回事？
你在说什么？
要是我们能打到下一轮的话
我还想再打个连赌  就这样
但我们打不到下一轮的……
- 这张牌是我打的 - 不  是我打的
- 是我打的  我出了J - 你放了面包屑
和大蒜在牛排里面  然后用牙签卷起来？
没错  然后再烤上三小时左右
一切都好  一切都好  我知道  你很郁闷
不  兰迪在抱怨  你也知道他输了很多钱
他在唉声叹气
餐厅的事多亏了兰迪  一切都好
谢谢观赏
改编自马修・泰勒的小说
-=TLF字幕组=-
http://sub.eastgame.org/ http://www.weibo.com/tlfsubs